--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：嘿疯
翻译：煦煦 D调的张扬 草长莹霏 RK翔 小花~  回声 CHI
校对：柚子茶 月光取暖
I get to work before the sun comes up and I leave long after it's gone down.
我每天起早贪黑 拼了命地工作
I haven't had sex in six months with someone other than myself.
除了我自已 我已经有六个月没和其他人做爱了
And the only thing in my refrigerator is an old lime.
我的冰箱里只有一个存放已久的酸橙
Could be a kiwi. No way to tell.
也可能是猕猴桃 我自已都忘了
- Morning, Thomas.  - Good morning, Nick. You better hurry.
- 早上好 Thomas  - 早上好 Nick 赶紧上去吧
But here's the thing
但问题是
This is just temporary.
这些都只是暂时的
Quick story
有个小故事
My grandmother came to this country with $20 in her pocket.
我的祖母来到这个国家的时候口袋里只有20美金
She worked hard her whole life and never took shit from anyone.
她拼命工作了一辈子 从不受任何人的气
When she died, she turned that $20 into $2000.
她去世的时候 口袋里的钱成了2000美金
That sucks.
太衰了
You know why she didn't succeed?
你们知道她为什么没有成功吗?
Because she didn't take shit from anyone.
正因为她从不受别人的气
The key to success...
成功的关键...
They will not teach you this in business school... is taking shit.
是商学院的老师们无法教给你们的... 就是忍气吞声
That's exactly what I've been doing the last eight years, and it's all about to pay off.
我已足足忍了八年 很快就要熬出头了
This is Nick.
我是Nick
I'm this close to getting a big promotion with my own office.
我即将得到晋升 拥有自己独立的办公室
I'll be right there, Mr. Harken.
我马上就到 Harken先生
Then all the endless hours, and the sacrifice and the shit-eating...
到那时无止境的工作 我的牺牲 还有我受的一肚子气...
will have been worth it.
就变得值得了
See, this is what concerns me, Nick.
看看 Nick 这就是我感到奇怪的事
You're a punctual guy. You know the importance of being here right at 6 a.m.
你是个很准时的员工 你清楚地知道每天早上六点准时到公司的重要性
Which is what leads me to think that...
所以我认为...
there must be something wrong with the internal clock on our security system.
我们公司安全系统的钟是不是坏了
May have been a minute late.
我可能是晚了一分钟
But according to this, you were two minutes late. So either you're a liar...
但是按上面显示的 你是迟了两分钟 所以要么是你撒谎...
or this system is off by a full minute.
要么是这个系统快了整整一分钟
The only hitch?
唯一的大麻烦?
I work for this guy, David Harken...
是这个家伙 我的老板 David Harken...
who right now is giving me some fresh shit for being two minutes late.
他现在正因为我迟到了两分钟而向我兴师问罪
He's a total fucking asshole.
他是一个彻头彻尾的混蛋
If that's the case, then I'm gonna have to fire Thomas, our longtime security coordinator.
如果是那样的话 我就必须开除一直呆在公司的安全协调员Thomas了
- I may have been two minutes late.  - Oh.
- 我可能是晚了两分钟  - 噢
Well, then you were lying.
所以 你刚才在撒谎了
No. I... Who you calling?
不是的 我... 你在给谁打电话?
- Thomas. I gotta let him go.  - No, uh...
- Thomas 我要让他走  - 不要 嗯...
- I was lying.  - You were lying?
- 我刚才在撒谎  - 是吗?
I didn't mean to. It was more of a saying. "Might have been a minute late."
我不是故意的 我只是顺口说了一句 "可能是晚了一分钟"
Literally, uh, truthfully, was two minutes late.
事实上 嗯 我的确是晚到了两分钟
Boy, I have to get used to driving with this big, heavy ring on my finger.
亲爱的 我现在必须习惯手指上套着这支又大又重的钻戒开车了
- Come on.  - I keep swerving to the left, babe.
- 拜托  - 我总是偏向左边 亲爱的
When I was a kid, people would ask me what I wanted to be when I grew up.
我小的时候 别人常问我长大后想要做什么
I always gave the same answer.
我的答案只有一个
I love you so much.
我好爱你
I love you too.
我也爱你
I wanted to be a husband.
我想成为一个丈夫
- I will call you when I'm done. - Have a good day.
- 我下班了打电话给你  - 工作愉快哦
I know that sounds weird.
我知道这听起来很奇怪
Most boys wanna be firehouse chiefs or personal trainers...
多数男人都想成为消防队队长或者私人教练...
but to me being a husband was, like, the highest calling.
但对我来讲 成为一个丈夫就好像是 最高使命
And thanks to Stacy...
托Stacy的福...
that dream's about to come true.
我这个梦就快要实现了
Unfortunately, no one's gonna pay you to be a husband unless you marry Oprah.
不幸的是 除非你要娶的是奥普拉 不然没人会因为你成为一个丈夫而付你钱
So I had to find a job.
所以我必须有一份工作
Now, I always admired dentists.
我一直都很崇拜牙医
They're smart, they're capable, they keep your teeth healthy.
他们聪明 能干 而且能让人们的牙齿保持健康
So I went out and I became one.
所以我也应聘成了其中一位
- How are you today, Dale?  - I'm fine. Thanks.
- 你今天好吗 Dale?  - 很好 谢谢
Excavator.
打洞机
Okay, I became a dental assistant. It's basically the same thing.
好吧 我成了一名牙医助理 其实差不多的
I just make a lot less money.
只是我挣的钱少一些
Did you ever see that show Gossip Girl?
你看过绯闻女孩这个节目吗?
- No.  - Ooh.
- 没有  - 噢
I watched an episode last night.
我昨晚看了一集
I fingered myself so hard to that Penn Badgley guy, I broke a nail.
我用手指拼命伸向那个叫Penn Badgley的家伙 还弄坏了一个指甲
And it would have been the perfect job. If not for one...
这会是一份很棒的工作 但前提是你的上司不是一个...
evil crazy bitch, D.D.S.
让人作呕的疯婊子 而且还是个牙科博士
I bet you're no shrimp in the cock department, huh, there, Dale?
我猜你的勃起功能应该不赖吧 嗯 Dale?
- Okay, Julia. Come on.  - What?
- 好了 Julia 别这样  - 怎么了?
- I'm uncomfortable talking about that. - Oh, Dale, come on.
- 我不喜欢谈这个  - 噢 Dale 拜托
You know that I like to fool around.
你知道我喜欢和别人乱来
- Oops.  - Mr. Anderton.
- 噢  - Anderton先生
Not in the office. This is bad.
别在办公室里这样 太下流了
- Bad, bad, bad!  - You probably shouldn't hit the patients.
- 下流 下流 下流!  - 你不该打病人吧
Ah, I love this. So festive.
啊 我太喜欢了 真让人兴奋
I love my job.
我热爱我的工作
If you ask me, anyone who hates their job has no one to blame but themself.
如果你问我为什么有些人讨厌他们的工作 我会说这只能怪他们自已 不能怪别人
We make our own destinies, and I've made a sweet one.
我们创造着自已的命运 而我的命运是很美好的
We have stairs. You don't need to bring your own.
我们有梯子 你不用带你自已的过来
I'm an account manager at a chemical company. I'll tell you something, the job has its perks.
我是一间化学公司的财务经理 我想告诉你 这份工作能使人振奋精神
Hi, can I help you?
嗨 我能帮你吗?
I am good. He's just signing for these packages. Thank you.
不用 他在这些包裹上签名 谢谢
Oh, no. I should do this.
噢 别 应该我来做
Reggie, I got this. Thank you, buddy.
Reggie 我来吧 谢了 伙计
- This is high-priority stuff here.  - Thank you.
- 这件事应该优先做才对  - 谢谢
- So, what's going on here?  - I'm sorry?
- 那么 这是在干什么?  - 什么?
- Is this one of those hidden camera shows?  - What do you mean?
- 这是一档隐藏拍摄的节目吗?  - 你是什么意思?
What I mean is like you're way too cute to be just a FedEx girl.
我的意思是你这么靓 送快递太可惜了
You gotta be a model or actress or something, right?
你应该成为一个模特 或是演员 或是其它的什么人物 对吧?
What happens when I open these boxes? Something'll jump out, bite my penis?
我打开这些盒子的时候会发生什么事? 有东西会跳出来咬我的小弟弟吗?
No. Nothing's gonna jump out. I'm just a FedEx girl.
不 没有东西会跳出来 我只是个送快递的女孩
- Shut up.  - Ha, ha.
- 闭嘴  - 哈 哈
- Bye.  - Have a great afternoon.
- 再见  - 祝你有个愉快的下午
Thank you.
谢谢
I didn't actually sign that form, by the way, so she has to come back.
其实我并没有签那张单子 所以她还会回来
She's cute, huh, Reg?
她很正 是吧 Reg?
- Caught another fly in your web, did you? - Ha, ha. Hey, Jack.
- 你又捕到一个猎物了 是吧?  - 哈 哈 嘿 Jack
But the real reason I'm here is this guy
但我做这份工作的真正原因是这个男人
Jack Pellit, my boss. The sweetest man I know.
我的老板 Jack Pellit 我所认识的最可爱的男人
He loves me and I love him. Everybody loves him.
他喜欢我 我也喜欢他 每个人都喜欢他
- You all right, Margie?  - Hi, Mr. Pellit. Kurt.
- 你没事吧 Margie?  - 嗨 Pellit先生 Kurt
I've been waiting to get in there for a while.
我已经在外面等很久了
- Who's in there?  - It's your son.
- 谁在里面?  - 你的儿子
Bobby!
Bobby啊!
Margie's waiting. You nearly done in there?
Margie等着呢 你快好了吗?
A man can't get any privacy around here.
在这里都没办法有一点隐私
- Okay, Margie. Bobby?  - What?
- 好了 Margie 喂 Bobby?  - 什么事?
Your stomach okay? You seem to spend more time on the toilet...
你的胃没事吧? 你在厕所里呆的时间好像...
than at your desk.
比在办公桌旁的还长
I didn't realize I had to tell you every time I wanna take a dump.
我不知道我每次想要大便的时候还得向你报告
If the worst thing about this job is having to tolerate my boss's...
对于这份工作 最糟糕的就是我必须忍受老板的...
dipshit cokehead son, well, it's a small price to pay.
混蛋傻X儿子 不过 就算是一点小小的付出吧
Need me to tell you when I am gonna pee-pee?
需要我在小便之前向你汇报吗?
I'm just trying to get you to do your part, son. It's not easy times.
我只想让你做好自已的工作 儿子 做生意没那么容易
I do my part. I do other people's parts.
我有做 我连其他人的工作都做
But it doesn't matter to you. Because You just wanna ride my ass because I'm your son.
但你根本不在意 因为我是你的儿子 所以你只想找我的茬
You know what? I don't hear you giving dickskin any shit.
你知道吗? 我从来没听你骂过这个狗家伙
- "Dickskin"? Nice.  - Kiss-ass.
- "狗家伙"? 很好  - 拍马屁的家伙
- Come on, come on.  - Yeah, go on. In you go.
- 走吧 走吧  - 是的 走吧 快滚吧
Get in the fucking... !
去他妈的滚吧... !
- I'm a green belt, motherfucker. - What?
- 我是一片绿化带 你他妈的  - 什么?
- Yeah. All right?  - Okay.
- 是的 怎么样?  - 算了
Now, I know you've been working your tail off for that promotion.
我知道你费尽心血地想要得到晋升机会
But I'm not sure I can even consider...
但我现在有些犹豫...
making you the senior vice president of sales...
是否让你成为销售高级副总裁
if I can't trust you.
除非你信得过
- You can trust me.  - Yeah, now you sound like my wife.
- 你可以相信我  - 嗯 你的口气听起来像我妻子
"Trust me. You can trust me, honey.
"相信我 你可以相信我 亲爱的
Nothing's happening behind your back. You can trust me."
我没有在你背后做出任何事 相信我吧"
Meanwhile, she's fucking every guy in the neighborhood.
但她一边说 一边和隔壁的每个男人上床
Oh, you want one?
噢 要来一杯吗?
It's 8:15 a.m.
现在是早上8:15
Well, is there something wrong with a man enjoying a drink in the morning?
一个男人早上享受美酒有什么问题吗?
No.
没有
- Thank you.  - Sure, thanks.
- 谢谢  - 很好 谢谢
Bottoms up.
干了它
Nothing for you?
你不要吗?
Nick, it's 8:15 in the morning. I'm not an alcoholic.
Nick 现在是早上8:15 我不是个酒鬼
Mr. Harken, the only reason I took one, because I thought you were gonna have one.
Harken先生 我打算喝的原因 是因为我以为你也会喝一杯
You took one because you thought I was gonna have one? Is that something a senior VP would do?
你喝是因为你以为我也会喝? 这是一个高级副总裁会做的事吗?
I was just trying to be polite.
我只是客气而已
So what? If I, uh, was gonna put my balls in honey and shaved coconut...
这么说吧? 如果我 嗯 打算把我的小弟弟放进蜂蜜和剖开的椰子里...
you'd do that too?
你也会照做吗?
- I would not. - Sure?
- 我不会  - 确定吗?
- Yeah.  - Because I've got some coconut.
- 是的  - 因为我有一些椰子
Anyway, I'm having my teeth whitened on Tuesday. So you gonna have to get your work done by Monday...
我打算星期二去将牙齿洗白 所以你必须在周一之前把工作都完成...
which means you'll probably have to be here all weekend.
这意味着你可能整个周末都得呆在这儿了
Look, if you want a promotion, you gotta earn it.
听着 如果你想要晋升 你必须付出努力
Now, what do I keep saying?
我一直说什么来着?
Life is a marathon, and you cannot win a marathon...
生活是一场马拉松比赛 如果你的乳头上没有贴几个邦迪...
without putting a few Band-Aids on your nipples, right?
你是没办法赢这场马拉松的 对吧?
Right.
对的
Nick.
Nick啊
It's 18-year-old Scotch.
这是存放了18年的苏格兰酒
You don't really expect me to pour it back into the bottle, do you?
你不是想我把它再倒回瓶子里吧 是吗?
- Water.  - Yep.
- 水  - 好的
All right. Let's see if this thing's working. Oh!
好了 让我们看看这个机器是不是正常工作 噢!
- Oh, my God.  - Oh! I'm sorry. I'm a squirter, Dale.
- 噢 天啦  - 噢! 对不起 我是一个喷射器 Dale
- Oh, you know what?  - What?
- 噢 你知道吗?  - 什么?
Ah. I think I can make out our little friend right there.
啊 我想我可以让你的小弟弟显现出来
Stop it.
停下来
- Somebody's circumcised.  - Okay.
- 原来你割过包皮啊  - 好了
- Listen.  - What?
- 听着  - 什么?
- Can we stop doing this thing here?  - Why? Because you have a girlfriend?
- 我们可以停止做这种事吗?  - 为什么? 因为你有女朋友?
She's not just my girlfriend anymore. We're engaged now.
她已经不再仅仅是我女朋友了 我们订婚了
- What?  - We're engaged.
- 什么?  - 我们订婚了
You said that she was just a hole for your dick.
你说过她只是让你的睾丸可以伸进去的一个洞而已
I never said that.
我从没说过
Not really my style.
这不是我的风格
Shut up.
闭嘴
That's a lot of gas.
你放了不少气哦
- That's good. No, those are great ideas.  - Yeah?
- 很好 不 这些点子太棒了  - 是吗?
- Put them down on paper, will you?  - Will do.
- 把它们写出来 可以吗?  - 我会的
- You're happy here, aren't you?  - Yeah, of course.
- 你在这里开心吧 不是吗?  - 是的 当然了
Good.
很好
You got a bright future here, you know?
你在公司的前途一片光明 你知道的吧?
Someday soon, it'll be you running this place.
不久的将来 你将会管理这家公司
- See you, kid.  - All right, now.
- 再见 孩子  - 好的
- Drive safe. - Yeah.
- 小心开车  - 好的
Oh, shit.
噢 该死的
He had a heart attack.
他心脏病发了
They said his, uh, heart burst in his chest like a water balloon.
他们说他的 呃 心脏就像个水球一样在他的胸口爆开了
Oh, my God. I'm sorry, man. I know you guys were close.
噢 天啦 对不起 伙计 我知道你们俩关系很好
Yeah. Yeah, I loved that guy.
是的 是的 我喜欢那个人
I loved working for him, you know? It was, like, awesome.
我喜欢为他工作 你知道吗? 就是 感觉特棒
Now his shitbag son's gonna be in charge and it's like--
现在他的屎蛋儿子就要接手了 也就是...
The cokehead?
那个蠢货?
Yeah. Know how many times I caught him doing blow at work?
是的 你知道我有多少次都抓到他工作的时候和女人打飞机吗?
This thing's a real bummer. Sorry. You're the only one of us who didn't hate his job.
太糟了 这么说真对不起 你是我们几个里面唯一不讨厌自已工作的
Did I tell you that Harken tricked me into having a drink at 8:00 this morning?
我有告诉你们那个混蛋Harken故意诱使我今天早上8点喝酒吗?
I mean, I work for the Antichrist.
我是说 我在给一个反基督者做事
- How did he trick you?  - I thought he was gonna give you a promotion.
- 他怎么诱使你的?  - 我以为他准备升你的职
He is, definitely. That's why he's being extra evil.
的确是 所以他才会更加可恶
You know, this is the last chance he has to make my life miserable.
因为这是他可以折磨我的最后机会
Right. At least your boss isn't sexually harassing you.
也对 至少你的老板没有对你性骚扰
- oh. My god. Here we go.  - Don't give me shit.
- 噢 天啦 又来了  - 别这么说我
You won't get any sympathy for this.
我们不会因为这个而同情你
She's going crazy. It's like a totally hostile work environment now, man.
她疯了 现在那就是一个硝烟四起的工作场所 伙计们
- It's not funny. - Yeah?
- 一点都不好玩  - 是吗?
All right, today she starts spraying water at my crotch to see the outline of my dick.
好吧 今天她把水喷到我的裤裆上 看我小弟弟的轮廓
- That's great. - It's not great.
- 太好玩了  - 一点都不好玩
What are you talking about? Why don't you just, you know, fuck her?
你在说什么? 你为什么不 就是 干脆上了她?
Because I am engaged to be married and I love my fiance, okay?
因为我已经订婚 马上就要结婚了 而且我爱我的未婚妻 懂了吗?
That's true.
很对
- Congratulations.  - Thank you.
- 恭喜你  - 谢谢
What about if you get a different dental hygienist job?
你去找另外一份牙科保健的工作怎么样?
I can't get another job.
我找不到另外一份
- No, he's a child molester, Nick.  - No, uh, deviant. Sexual deviant?
- 不 他是儿童性骚扰者 Nick  - 不 啊 变态 性变态者
What is it? How do they classify it? Sex offender.
怎么说的? 别人怎么称呼这种人? 性侵者
I'm on the registered sex offender list, yes.
对 我留了案底 被指性侵
You can't get that expunged? All you did was pull your dick out on a playground.
你怎么不为自己伸冤? 你只不过是在操场上裸露了下半身
I was taking a piss at night, there were no kids.
我那天晚上在撒尿 旁边根本没有小孩
All right, you know what? You don't put a playground right next to a bar.
好吧 你知道吗? 千万别把操场建在酒吧旁边
- It's entrapment.  - Mm-hm.
- 那样会惹祸上身  - 嗯哼
Speaking of entrapment, I'm gonna go see that girl about her vagina.
说到上身 我打算过去探一探那个女孩的阴道
Excuse me.
失陪了
He did say 10:00, right?
他说了是10点钟 是吧?
Yeah. Do you know what this is about?
没错 你知道今天开什么会吗?
It just said "staff meeting" on the memo.
备忘录上只写了"员工会议"
It's funny how he gets all over my ass if I'm a minute late,
真可笑 我迟到一分钟他就要找我的茬儿
but then he makes us wait 15.
可现在他却让我们干等了15分钟
You were two minutes late, Nick. Morning.
你实际上迟到了2分钟 Nick 早上好
And I didn't think I had to punch a clock with you.
我可不想给你装台闹钟在身上
You don't.
当然不用
I'll just attribute this to your drinking problem.
这些都是由于你酗酒造成的
I don't have...
我没有...
Nick, Please, we're in the middle of a meeting.
Nick 拜托 我们正在开会
Morning, everyone. So I have finally decided...
大家早上好 我终于决定了...
who I want to be our new senior vice president of sales.
我们的新任销售高级副总裁人选
He's right here in this room.
此刻他就在这个房间内
- It's me.  - What'd he say?
- 就是我  - 他说什么?
I've decided to absorb the responsibilities...
我已决定将高级副总裁的责任...
of the senior VP position into my own.
承担在自己肩上
I've realized if you wanna get something done right,
我意识到如果你想让某件事进展顺利
you gotta do it yourself.
你就得亲自去做
So I'll break through the wall of the office
所以我会打穿那堵本来属于
that would have been the senior VP's...
高级副总裁办公室的墙...
and make one huge, enormous office.
然后造一个更大 更宽敞的办公室
However, I will only be taking 85 percent
不过 至于我那份额外的工资
of the additional salary I am entitled to...
我只会拿其中的85%...
and that is self-sacrifice, people. Learn from it.
这就是自我牺牲 伙计们 学着点
Fucker!
贱人!
You fucking son of a bitch!
你个婊子养的!
You are so fucking fired!
你他妈的被炒了!
Yeah!
好啊!
So, meeting adjourned.
好的 会议结束
- Mr Harken Can I speak to you?  - Yes, sure, what is it?
- Harken先生 我可以跟你谈谈吗?  - 当然 谈什么?
For months you've been hinting...
几个月以来你一直在暗示...
that I was in line for that promotion.
我是升任这个职位的人选
And look how hard you've been working.
所以看你工作得多么认真啊
- You were just lying to me?  - Lying?
- 难道你只是在耍我?  - 耍你?
No, Nick, motivating.
不 Nick 是激励
I mean, look, we're all part of the same team here.
我是说 看看 我们都是这个团队的一员
Plus, you know,
还有 你清楚
I'm the one who's gonna be doing all the extra work.
我才是将要承担所有额外工作的人
You know that last month you made me work so late...
你知道吗 上个月你总让我工作到非常晚...
I missed saying goodbye to my Gam Gam?
以至于我连跟Gam Gam道别的机会都错过了?
- Sorry, what?  - My grandmother.
- 抱歉 你说什么?  - 是我的祖母
I told you I needed to see her because she was very sick.
我说过我得见她 因为她病得非常厉害
You said if I left early, I'd get fired.
而你说要是我提早离开 我就会被炒鱿鱼
And she died before I made it to the hospital.
结果在我到医院之前她就去世了
- I'm sorry.  - Thank you.
- 真遗憾  - 谢谢
I had no idea that you called your grandmother "Gam Gam."
我真搞不懂你居然管你的祖母叫"Gam Gam"
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
抱歉 抱歉
I'm sorry you didn't get to say bye-bye to Gam Gam.
真遗憾你没能跟你的Gam Gam说再见
Really, I really am. I'm sorry.
真的 我认真的 我很遗憾
But I needed you to work late...
但我需要你工作到很晚...
because you are an invaluable member of this operation.
因为你是这个项目不可或缺的一员
And I need you in the position you're currently in.
你必须坚守你目前的岗位
Well, tough shit, okay?
听着 都是废话 行吗?
I've been in that position for eight years.
我已经在这个职位待了八年
Now why would I stay after being treated like this?
如今遭到这样的待遇 凭什么还指望我为你工作?
Well, because I'd make sure that...
因为我确信...
nobody in the industry would ever hire you again.
这行业中没人会再雇用你
Bullshit.
放屁
No, because they're gonna want my letter of recommendation, right?
错 因为他们总得要我的推荐信 是吧?
So I'm perfectly willing to write that...
所以我很乐意地写上...
you are an insubordinate, dishonest drunk.
你是个不听指挥 不诚实的醉鬼
You can't do that. That's not true.
你不能这样做 这不是真的
Let me tell you something, you stupid little runt.
给我听好 你个小傻瓜蛋
I own you.
我是你老板
You're my bitch.
你是我的狗
Don't walk around here thinking you have free will...
在我的公司 就得听我的...
because you don't.
你没有自由
I can crush you any time I want.
只要愿意 我随时都能弄死你
So settle in because you are here for the long haul.
所以该干嘛干嘛去 因为你注定要在这待一辈子
Yo, dickwall.
嘿 小样
- What the fuck?  - What?
- 你在搞什么鬼?  - 怎么了?
Three hours late. What's the deal?
你迟到了三小时 什么情况?
- I was at your father's funeral.  - Uh-huh. Mm-hm.
- 我刚去参加了你父亲的葬礼  - 啊 嗯
Well, maybe that excuse would have flown when my dad was here,
很好 我老爸在的时候这个借口应该管用
but I'm in charge now.
但是现在我说了算
That excuse wouldn't make any sense...
如果你老爸还在...
if your dad was still here.
那这个借口就说不通了
Whoa.
喔
In my office, now.
到我办公室来 马上
Yes?
什么?
All right, sit.
好的 坐
- I'm not a dog, Bobby.  - Good boy.
- 我不是条狗 Bobby  - 乖孩子
I've been looking through the books.
我一直在看这些册子
You're the accountant. Tell me...
你是会计师 那告诉我...
why is this company in the crapper?
为什么我们公司在亏损?
Well, we're not in the crapper.
其实 我们并没有亏损
- It's a recession, but we're still profitable.  - Bullshit.
- 只是经济不景气 但我们还在盈利  - 放屁
Look...
瞧...
I know you and my dad were, uh, pals. Okay?
我知道你和我老爸曾经是 呃 好友 是吧?
Frankly, I always thought it was a little bit weird and gay.
说实话 我一直觉得那关系有点怪怪的 就像同志间的那种
I have no idea why he thought you were so fucking special.
我真不懂他为嘛总觉得你丫的那么特别
But that doesn't matter now, he's in the ground.
不过现在这不打紧了 他已经翘辫子了
Guess what, I'm your boss.
猜怎么着 我现在是你的头儿
And there's gonna be some changes around here.
这里得有一些改变才行
- Can't wait to hear them.  - OK, first things first.
- 迫不及待想听听是什么  - 好 先说重要的
EnviroTech Waste Management, we'll fuck this...
我们得先灭了环保处理措施...
because it's costing us a lot of money.
因为这是很大一笔开销
Your dad made the choice...
妥善处理化学废物...
to dispose of our chemical waste responsibly.
这是你老爸的决定
Inorder to do that, you gotta spend a lot of money.
要这样做 你就得舍得花钱
Bolivians will do it for a third of the price.
这活只用出三分之一的价钱波利维亚人就肯做
I'm gonna hire them.
我打算雇他们
- No, no, You can't go to them, you should'nt do this.  - Why?
- 不 你不能雇他们 你不能这样做 - 为什么?
Because they're gonna endanger thousands of local residents.
因为这样会对数以万计的当地居民造成威胁
Oh, I give a fuck some local tribesman gets cancer.
就算这些当地土著得癌症又怎样
Cry me a fucking river.
我连自己都顾不过来
They're not tribesmen. It's a modern society.
他们不是土著 这是现代社会
Do I look like I fucking care?
我丫的看上去有在乎吗?
OK, all right, look, Bobby.
好的 听着 Bobby
Your dad told me very clearly he would rather die...
你老爸明确地告诉过我他宁愿死...
than save money and hurt people, okay?
也不愿以牺牲别人为代价来赚钱 懂吗?
Well, guess what,
好吧 猜怎么着
looks like we're right on schedule, doesn't it?
就照我说的做 懂吗?
OK, what else?
好了 还有什么?
Oh yeah, we gotta trim some of the fat around here.
噢 对了 是时候该清理清理这里的肥猪了
Trim the... What do you mean by "trim the fat"?
清理... 你说"清理肥猪"是什么意思?
- I want you to fire the fat people.  - What?
- 我想把那些胖子给炒了  - 什么?
They're lazy, and slow and they make me sad to look at.
他们又懒又慢 一看到他们我就抓狂
You can start with Large Marge.
你可以先拿肥姐Marge开刀
Marge, can you come in here, please?
Marge 请到我办公室来好吗?
No, Margie's not fat, she's pregnant.
不 Marge不是胖 她只是怀孕了
I'm not gonna fire her.
我不会炒了她的
Well, fine. Uh...
好吧 行 呃...
stay where you are, Marge. Congratulations.
不用进来了 Marge 祝贺你
You can fire, uh, Professor Xavier.
你可以炒了 呃 Xavier教授
Who are you talking about?
你在说谁?
- You mean Hank?  - Yeah.
- 你是说Hank?  - 没错
Fucking creeps me out,
他丫的把我逼疯了
rolling around all day in his special secret chair.
每天坐着他那特制的神秘轮椅四处转来转去
- I know he's up to something.  - I won't fire anyone.
- 我知道他一定在密谋什么  - 我不会炒了任何人的
- You're not? Oh, really?  - Yeah, really.
- 你不干? 噢 是吗?  - 没错 是的
You know, it's like you don't care about this company at all.
似乎你根本不在乎这个公司
No fucking shit I don't care about this company.
去他妈的我当然不在乎这个公司
This... this is just an ATM to me.
这... 这只不过是我的自动取款机而已
You think when I was a kid...
你难道认为...
I dreamed of running a fucking chemical company?
我从小的梦就是经营一个该死的化学公司吗?
No. I dreamed of being on a beach...
不 我梦想的是待在沙滩上...
with a model serving me tropical drinks.
旁边还有美女拿着热带饮品服侍我
That's what I dreamed of. And that's what's gonna happen...
这就是我想要的 一旦我从这个公司榨出福利...
as soon as I squeeze the profit out of this fucking company.
这一切就将成为现实
But first things first.
但最重要的是
You either fire the fatty or you fire the cripple,
你要是不炒了那个肥猪或者是那个瘸子
or I fire all three of you.
我就把你们三个都炒了
Do the math.
算一算
One loses the job or three loses it.
哪个更加划算
And tell him to leave his handicap parking pass here as well.
记得告诉他留下他的残疾人泊车通行证
Come in.
进来
Julia, you needed to see me?
Julia 你找我有事吗?
Oh, shit.
噢 见鬼
Uh-oh.
啊呃
- Will you have a seat, Dale?  - Do I have to?
- 你不打算坐下吗 Dale?  - 我非得坐吗?
Please.
请吧
Sure.
好的
This is a little ridiculous, but...
这有点可笑 不过...
Look, Dale, you know,I...
瞧 Dale 你知道我...
You know that I like to fool around at work. Right?
你知道我工作的时候很随性 是吧?
And I might even... You know,
而且我甚至... 你知道
I might even cross the line a bit.
我甚至会有点出格
But the last thing that I wanna do is make you uncomfortable.
但我绝对不想为难你
I mean, it's just not professional. You know?
我是说 这样做只是有点不大专业 你明白吗?
And I pride myself on being a professional.
而我以自己的专业性为骄傲
So from now on,
所以从现在起
what I would like you to do is just..just tell me, you know...
我想让你做的就是...就是告诉我 你知道...
when and if, uh, I cross the line. Okay?
我什么时候以及是否 呃 出格了 行吗?
Okay. Now.
行 现在
What?
什么?
Well, now, you're kind of crossing a line...
呃 现在 你就有点出格了...
because you're naked.
因为你裸了
Uh...
呃...
Not naked, Dale.
这不算裸 Dale
- Can you see my pussy?  - Hmm.
- 你有看到我的阴户了吗?  - 嗯
True. Um...
的确 呃...
But I think, uh, even really saying the word "pussy" is...
但我觉得 呃 即便是说"阴户"这个词也是...
- That's crossing the line?  - Little bit.
- 这算出格了吗?  - 有点
You're starting to sound like a little faggot.
你说话的口气开始有点像个同志了
There we go. That one's another one,
好了 说说另一件事
probably illegal thing to say too.
说起来可能也有点出格
Okay. Let's not talk about illegal,
听着 我们还是不要说什么出格了吧
Mr. I-Like-To-Pee-On-Little-Boys.
你不也喜欢对着小男孩撒尿吗
It was an empty playground in the middle of the night.
当时我以为操场上没有别人
Ah. That's even weirder.
啊 这更奇怪了
That poor child must have been terrified.
那可怜的小孩一定吓得够呛
There were no children. No kids in the park.
根本没有什么孩子在公园操场上
Why do people think that?
人们为什么会这样想?
You know what? Forget it.
你猜怎么着? 忘了这件事吧
Listen, let's just cut to the chase, all right, mister?
听着 这件事到此为止 行吗 先生?
- You're engaged now.  - Right.
- 你已经订婚了  - 是的
And I respect the institution of marriage...
我十分尊重婚姻制度...
way too much to violate it.
所以我不想破坏它
So that's why...
这就是为什么...
you're gonna have to fuck me well before the wedding.
你才一定要在婚礼之前干我
Because the closer we get to this date,
因为越是临近婚期
the less ladylike I'm gonna feel about it.
我就越难保持淑女形象
Julia, I'm not gonna sleep with you.
Julia 我不会跟你上床的
We'll see about that.
等着瞧吧
Get out.
出去
Could you do the, uh...?
你可不可以 呃...?
I'm a sucker. Harken wasn't gonna promote me.
我真是个衰人  Harken根本不打算提升我
That coked-up prick is gonna ruin Pellit Chemicals.
那个败家子会毁了Pellit化工厂的
He's just gonna fire everybody.
他会炒了所有的人
She stood there with her breasts right in my face.
她就那样站着 胸部直对着我的脸
Yeah, you know, yours doesn't sound that bad.
是啊 知道吗 你的故事根本没那么糟糕
I'll stop bringing it up.
那我不说了
I don't understand why you guys don't just quit.
我不懂你们几个干嘛不干脆辞职
Julia's the only one who'd hire me.
Julia是唯一一个愿意雇我的人
Are you registered sex offenders?
难到你们也被列入了性侵犯者名单吗?
Going back to school, changing fields, starting from the bottom.
跳槽意味着重新上培训班  从基层做起
Who wants to do that?
谁会愿意这样做?
What do I care about protecting Pellit's name...
连Pellit的亲儿子都不在意他的招牌...
when his own son doesn't? You know?
我干嘛要这么卖力? 知道吗?
- Gotta be a million jobs out there.  - You could find another job.
- 此处不留爷自有留爷处  - 你可以换个工作
Is this really happening? Look at this. Oh!
这是真的吗? 看啊 噢!
The Three Musketeers. Nick, Kurt and Dale.
是三个火枪手 Nick Kurt和Dale
Look, you guys hanging like high school.
瞧 你们几个还像高中一样混在一起
Oh, shit. Kenny's here. What's up?
噢 见鬼 是Kenny 最近怎么样?
- Yeah, I love this.  - Kenny Sommerfeld.
- 是啊 真高兴  - 是Kenny Sommerfeld
In the flesh, boys.  Oh, my goodness.
总算见到真人了 伙计们 噢 我的老天
- Now, I heard you moved to New York,  - Yeah
- 听说你去纽约了  - 没错
You're working at Lehman Brothers.
为雷曼兄弟公司做事
Yeah, yeah, they, uh, hired me right out of Yale.
是的 没错 他们 呃 我一从耶鲁毕业就雇了我
What are you doing here?
那你怎么在这?
You read the papers? They shut us down.
你看了报纸吧? 我们给放长假了
Yeah, sorry about that
是啊 挺遗憾的
I've been looking for work for the last two years.
过去两年我一直在找工作
It's crazy I can't even get a job waiting tables.
可我甚至连服务员的工作都找不到
Ah, you know what, though?
啊 结果你猜怎么着?
I would fucking murder those Lehman Brothers if I could.
要是可以的话我真他妈的想把那些雷曼兄弟给做了
Yeah, I hear you.
是啊 我懂
Ha. I can't even pay for this fucking drink.
哈 我甚至连这杯该死的酒都付不起
- Well, we'll cover it, right?  - Right.
- 没事 算我们来付 是吧?  - 没错
Seriously, uh, you guys think you could help me out a little?
说实在的 呃 你们觉得能不能帮我个小忙?
- Beyond the drink?  - Maybe some extra scratch, if you got it.
- 除了这杯酒?  - 也许可以借点闲钱给我 如果你们有的话
Of course. Kenny,
当然 Kenny
I had no idea it was that bad,buddy, all I got's 15.
我没想到你境况这么糟 老兄 我只有15了
- Do you have change for a 10?  - No, I don't.
- 你有零钱找散10元吗?  - 不 我没有
You know what?
你猜怎么着?
That's probably not gonna cut it, so I'll tell you what.
这肯定解决不了问题 我告诉你们该怎么办
How about I give you guys some hand jobs?
不如我帮你们打手枪怎么样?
- Do what?  - Forty bucks apiece.
- 干什么?  - 每个人40美元
We could do it here in the bathroom.
我们可以就在这的厕所里干
- No thanks.  - That's a joke? You're joking?
- 不 谢了  - 那是个冷笑话吗? 你在开玩笑对吧?
- Kenny.  - Hey!
- 嗨Kenny  - 嘿!
- Oh, shit.  - Come on, man.
- 噢 该死  - 过来 伙计
I told you no more handies in here.
我告诉过你不要再勾搭别人
You guys change your minds, I'm staying at my mom's house.
你们要是改变主意了 就来我妈妈家找我
Okay.
好的
Maybe don't quit your job.
你最好还是不要辞职了
I guess we'll be miserable for the rest of our lives.
我想我们下半辈子一定会很屎
That's the deal?
是这样吗?
- That's the way it's looking.  - Why you saying that?
- 看上去就是这样  - 为什么这么说?
We don't have many options, do we?
我们没多少选择 不是吗?
Think about it, we can quit our jobs and turn into Kenny...
想想看 我们可以辞了工作 然后变得像Kenny一样...
or, uh, keep our jobs and just become spineless losers...
或者 呃 在岗位上继续待下去 成为一个没骨气的失败者...
that spend their entire day...
每天都变着花样想着...
dreaming of ways to kill their bosses.
该怎么去做掉自己的老板
- You do that too?  - Of course.
- 你也这么想吗?  - 必须的
Sounds a little sick.
听起来很变态
It's not. It's just a way to blow off steam.
不是的 这不过是一种宣泄的方式
It's not like we're gonna actually kill our bosses.
我们不可能真的做了自己的老板的
- Good.  - Ha, ha. Though you would have to admit...
- 很好  - 哈哈 尽管你得承认...
that our lives would be
要是没了这些老板
a hell lot easier if our bosses weren't alive.
我们的日子会好过得多
Mm-hm.
嗯
Hypothetically, if we could do it...
假设 我们真可以这样做
and none of us get caught, would you guys do it?
而且没人会被抓 你们会动手吗?
- No.  - I would.
- 不会  - 我会
- No, you wouldn't.  - Yeah, I would.
- 不 你不会  - 是的 我会
- You would?  - Yeah.
- 你真会?  - 当然
It's not murder if it's justified.
如果是正当行为就构不成谋杀
Justifiable homicide, that's the thing, right?
正当杀人 就是这样 明白吗?
I can't wait to hear this.
真想听听是怎么回事
If one evil person has to die for the greater good, so be it.
如果为了正义得牺牲一个恶人的性命的话 那就去做吧
You know, Bobby Pellit is an absolute monster.
你知道 Bobby Pellit是个十足的禽兽
He's a fucking jerk.
他丫的就是个混蛋
You know, if he has his way,
知道吗 如果按他的想法行事
he's gonna end up killing thousands of innocent Bolivians.
他将会置数以万计无辜的的波利维亚人于死地
What?
什么?
Technically, I think it's immoral not to kill him.
严格来说 我认为留着他的小命 反而是件不道德的事
I should kill Harken for not letting me say goodbye to Gam Gam?
那我应该杀了Harken 因为他不让我和Gam Gam奶奶见最后一面?
Yes. Yes, you should.
没错 杀了他
But I don't care how bad our bosses are. We're not murderers.
我不在乎老板有多恶 我们又不是杀人犯
Julia is ruining your life, you know? That's wrong.
Julia把你的生活全毁了 这可不对
- That is wrong. - It's affecting your possible marriage.
- 是的 不对 - 对你以后的婚姻也有影响
- Come on, she's not ruining it. - Would your life be easier without Julia?
- 拜托 她哪有 - 如果你的生活里没她 会不会轻松很多?
Ok.You're right. Uh, know what I'm gonna do?
好吧 你说的都对 呃 知道我打算干吗?
I'm gonna go to Julia's house, maybe I'll slash her up...
去Julia家，对着她猛砍一顿
and I'll put her in a box and I'll mail it to you two, uh, tough-guy mafiosos.
塞进箱子 再寄给你两个恶棍黑手党
I'm done with this conversation. You're paying for dinner because you've upset me.
不聊了 今晚你请客 谁让你搞得我不爽
You're paying and I'm finding a cab somehow.
掏你的钱吧 我去叫计程车
I was just speaking hypothetically, you know.
我只是设想一下 你懂得
Me too.
我也一样
Guess who.
猜猜我是谁
Look, I'm really kind of not in the mood for this.
我现在没心情跟你玩这个
Not in the mood for what?
没心情玩哪个?
- Hi. - Hi, babe.
- 嗨 - 嗨 亲爱的
Oh, what are you doing here?
你怎么来了?
- I invited her. - Yes. She called.
- 我请她来的 - 她电话我的
And she said that now that we're engaged, she wanted to offer me free dental work.
她还说我们已经订婚了 要给我免费补牙
- And you know I have that loose filling.  - Yeah.
- 你知道我的牙该重新补了  - 是哦
This really was so, so sweet of you, Julia.
Julia 你可太好了
Oh, please. Come on, Stacy, it's my pleasure.
拜托 Stacy 我荣幸着呢
You're part of the family now.
你也是我们家一份子了
But, um, I don't know if it's a good idea, sweetie.
不过 亲爱的 这样恐怕不妥吧
Oh, why not?
为什么?
Because we're mixing pleasure with business. Business and pleasure.
因为我们把公事私事混为一谈了
We're taking advantage of Julia.
这可是在占Julia的便宜
Dale.
别这样 Dale
There's nothing that you could do ever that would be taking advantage of me.
不论你做什么都不算是占我的便宜
- Okay?  - So sweet.
- 行不?  - 她真好
All right, you. Let's go say we pump you full of gas, huh?
好了 小妞 过来把你的美牙补补齐
- Okay. - Okay.
- 好滴  - 好吧
Fuck me.
靠
Ten.
十
Nine.
九
I don't know what you're doing with your hand, babe
宝贝 你要摸哪里
- Okay.  - Seven.
- 听话  - 七
Put your hand in a safe place because there's sharp tools here.
把手放好了 这里都是危险物品
Oh, there she goes.
哦 她睡了
- Come here!  - What are you doing? What are you doing?
- 过来!  - 你要干嘛? 你要干嘛?
You're gonna give me that dong, Dale.
Dale 把你的鸡鸡给我
My dong?
鸡鸡?
You're gonna fuck my slutty little mouth.
用我的樱桃小嘴让你欲仙欲死
Do you hear the words you say sometimes? I mean, who talks like that?
你不会反思一下自己说的话吗? 哪个女人像你这样说话?
Let's have sex on top of her. Let's use her like a bed.
在她身上做吧 把她当成床
Get down, get down. Hey, hey! Get off of her.
下来 下来 嘿 你给我下来
God damn you! That's it, okay? You know what? That's crossing the line.
去你的! 够了 你又出格了
So I'm done, Julia.
我投降 Julia
Fuck this. I'm out. I don't need this job. So goodbye, I'm quitting. I'm done.
去他妈的 我退出 不干了 投降
I'm gonna tell her you fucked me.
那我就告诉她 咱俩上床了
What?
什么?
If you don't fuck me, I'm gonna tell her that you fucked me.
你不从我 我就骗她说 我们搞过了
Okay. Tell her whatever the hell you want. She's not gonna believe you.
好吧 你想说啥说啥 她才不信呢
She already knows that you're a sex offender.
她知道你是名性侵者
And I think once she gets a look at these...
一旦她看了这些...
she's gonna believe me.
就会相信了
- What is that?  - Do you remember your first week here, dale?
- 那又是什么?  - 你还记得刚来的第一个礼拜吗?
When I changed the crown on your second bicuspid?
我给你的尖牙换了齿冠?
Yeah.
记得
Well, I just, uh, took a few pictures of the procedure.
也没啥 就是手术时拍了几张照片
- Oh, my God.  - Right?
- 额滴神啊  - 拍得不错吧?
Oh, no. What?
不会吧
Oh. Ooh.
哦
You did all this while I was unconscious?
你在我被麻醉时干的?
Ooh. Mm-hm. Yep.
嗯 是滴
That's my favorite.
这张可是我的最爱
- Rape.  - What?
- 强奸  - 什么?
Rape. That's a rape. This is what raping is.
这就是强奸啊 强奸罪
You're a raper and you've raped me. That's a rape! Rape!
你个强奸犯把我上了 强奸! 强奸!
Just relax there, Jodie Foster.
放松点 朱迪・福斯特
(著名女演员,在《被告人中》成功塑造一个被强奸者,获奥斯卡最佳女演员奖)
Your dick wasn't even hard.
当时你都没硬
That does not give me any relief.
这又不能让我好受点
But it will be next time, and if it is not...
下次必须硬 如果还不...
this little sweetheart right here is gonna get a peek at my little photo album.
这个小美妞 就有机会大开眼界了
So please prep the patient for the bitewing x-ray.
帮病人准备做咬翼片X光吧
I'll be back in a jiffy.
我马上回
I'm in. Let's kill this bitch!
我加入 杀了那个贱人!
- What bitch?  - "What bitch"? Guys, my boss.
- 哪个贱人?  - "哪个贱人"? 当然是我老板了
Our bosses need to die. You were right, man. We should do this thing.
她必须死 你们说的对 我们得杀了她
We were drinking last night. As youeself said that killing is wrong.
昨晚只是酒后胡言 你自己也说杀人犯法
I know. I know. That was before Julia tried to fuck me on top of Stacy's unconscious body.
我知道 可昨晚她个贱人还没要求我 在Stacy被麻醉的身体上 上她
- Really? - Yes, dude.
- 不会吧? - 是真的
She's gone fucking batshit crazy. She took a bunch of photographs of me...
她个性变态 还拍了我的艳照
- Where are they?  - They'll ruin my life. I can't show them to you.
- 在哪呢?  - 我的人生全毁了 不能给你们看
- It's a whole thing. You guys in or out?  - I was in last night.
- 这事得一起干 你们干不干?  - 要是昨晚 我干
- Nick, what do you say? Let's do this.  - Please. Let's go.
- Nick 你干不? 干吧  - 行了吧 继续
Nick, come on.
Nick 拜托
Seriously. I mean, uh, what about your grandma, you know? Bubbe.
说真的 呃 你奶奶Bubbe呢?
- Gam Gam.  - Whatever it is.
- 是Gam Gam  - 管他了
She didn't get to say goodbye to her grandson.
她都没机会和孙子见最后一面
Why? Because his dickbag of a boss wouldn't let him leave. Right?
为啥? 因为该死的老板不准假
- What would Gam Gam want you to do?  - She wouldn't want me to kill him.
- 你奶奶希望你怎么做?  - 反正不是杀了老板
Okay, forget about Gam Gam. She's dead. You gotta accept that.
好吧 别想你奶奶了 她已经去了 节哀顺变
This is about you, Nick. Okay, what do you want?
关键在你 Nick 你想怎么做?
Well, obviously I want him gone.
我当然想他消失了
- Exactly. So let's do this.  - Right?
- 绝对 那就一起干吧  - 怎样?
- How do we do this?  - I thought about that.
- 怎么干?  - 我想过了
Stacy and I, we watch a ton of Law & Order.
我和Stacy是法律剧集的粉
There's all sorts of ways the bad guys on the show mess up, right?
罪犯作案后都会留下蛛丝马迹 对吧?
They leave behind skin cells and, uh, bullet casing--
他们留下皮肤细胞 子弹壳
Sperm.
精液
- Most of the time, it's sperm.  - Silent killer.
- 大多数都是精液  - 沉默杀手里就是这样
Anyway, that's not the point. Point is...
不管怎样 那不是重点 重点是...
we're not qualified. We gotta hire a professional.
我们不够格 得雇个专业的
- Are you talking about a hit man?  - Yeah.
- 你说职业杀手?  - 没错
That's a really good idea.
好主意
Yeah. We don't clean our own apartments or cut our own hair.
我们就用不着清理现场 或者乔装打扮
- No, we pay someone to do that.  - Yeah.
- 付钱让别人做  - 对
Uh, where are you two gonna find a hit man?
那你俩打算去哪找职业杀手?
Why don't you guys leave that up to me, okay?
这事就交给我吧
I got this whole thing figured out.
我来理清头绪
I'm gonna give you a call tomorrow, I'm gonna tell you where to meet me.
明天给你们电话 再定哪里碰面
Why don't you just tell us now?
为啥现在不说?
- Because I don't have it figured out.  - Ah.
- 我还没想好呢  - 了解
But I will.
很快
- Were you followed?  - Why would I be followed?
- 没人跟着吧?  - 谁跟我干嘛?
People follow people in these types of situations. Sure you weren't?
这会一般都有人跟踪的 确定没有?
Oh, boy. What people?
没有 什么人?
Just take one quick look around, make sure no one followed you here.
快点 四周看看 确定没人跟你来
- Let's put this down.  - Look around, make sure some...
- 快把锁打开  - 看看啊 确定...
- Calm down! Calm down!  - That's what you get.
- 冷静! 冷静!  - 你他妈自找的
Shut the door, take the chain off and let me in.
关门 打开锁链 让我进去
- I pissed him off already.  - Already?
- 我把他惹毛了  - 这么快
What the hell's going on with you, huh? What are we doing here?
你他妈发什么火 忘了我们的任务了?
- I don't want an assassin in my apartment.  - Don't want this guy knowing where we live, use your head.
- 我可不想自己家被刺客光顾  - 不想让那人知道我们住哪 动动脑子
Hang on a second, you guys already went ahead and found someone that's coming here?
hold住 你俩已经先行动 找到人了? 一会过来?
- Oh, bigtime.  - Not "we." Dale,I found a guy.  - All by himself.
- 哦 他可是大人物  - 不是"我们" Dale 是我找的  - 他自己
- It was pretty easy. Easy as buying a used futon.  - You found a hit man online?
- 小菜一碟 就像买二手床垫  - 你在网上找的职业杀手?
Yeah. They don't write "hit man," right? That's dumb.
是啊 在网上不叫"职业杀手" 那不是找死嘛
- They use code words, like wet work, right? Liquidation.  - Check him out.
- 他们用代号 就像湿身行动 讨债达人  - 看看这人
"Skilled professional with years of experience...
"具有多年国内外湿身行动经验
in domestic and international wet work.
技术专业...
Discreet. No children, no political figures."
行事谨慎 无孩 无党派人物"
That last part was important. I saw that, I thought, "This is a good idea."
最后那句重要 我看到就想 "就是他了"
I still feel we should've got a cheese plate for this guy. just to make...
我还是觉得应该给他准备些点心...
- 20/20 hindsight.  - Is that him?
- 早不说  - 他来了?
- Oh, shit.  - Yeah, that was definitely a car.
- 靠  - 有车来了
- He looks like James Bond.  - He really does, dude.
- 天哪 詹姆斯・邦德  - 还真像啊
I bet he carries a gun that you screw together. Those are, like, the coolest guns they make.
我敢赌他带枪了 那种最酷的枪
So dangerous. What if that is an undercover cop?
这可不是闹着玩的 要是卧底警察咋办?
- Come on.  - What if it's the real thing?
- 拜托  - 如果他真是职业杀手呢?
He charges so much we can't afford it, gets pissed, kills us.
他要价太高 我们付不起 毛了 杀了我们 就好玩了
- Kills all three of us?  - Hold on. That's a thing?
- 杀了我们仨?  - Hold住 还有这事?
Could that happen?
可能吗?
- Gotta let him in.  - How's my hair?
- 得让他进来啊  - 我发型咋样?
- What do you mean?  - It doesn't matter. Let's do this. Okay.
- 你啥意思?  - 别管了 上吧
Ready?
准备好了?
Yeah?
找谁?
Are you Dale?
你是Dale?
- I am the one they call Dale.  - Hmm.
- 他们叫我Dale  - 恩
Please come in.
请进
Thank you.
谢了
Are all three of you participating in this?
你们仨都要?
- Yes.  - Well, um....
- 是的  - 这个嘛....
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yep. Yep.  - Yes.
- 是的 是的  - 没错
Very well.
很好
Now, before we go any further...
在进一步行动之前...
I need to know if there are any hidden recording devices in the room.
我得确定房间里没有隐藏摄像头之类的
I will find out if there are.
如果有我也能找到
I'm sure you would, but there's none because that would be stupid of us.
你肯定能 不过真没有 那样我们太傻了
- That's a silly move.  - It's a no.
- 不是明智之举  - 没有
Then let's get started.
那我们就开始吧
- I love this guy.  - This is the real deal.
- 我喜欢他  - 这可是真生意啊
- His voice, you kidding?  - This guy is legit.
- 他的声音  - 这伙计还挺正规
And you do know that we just wanna start with a...?
你知道我们只是想从...开始?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, wait, what's this for?
哇 哇 等下 这干吗用的?
- For the mess.  - What?
- 清理废物  - 啥?
Wouldn't wanna leave a stain, now. Wouldn't me?
我可不想留下蛛丝马迹 对吧?
- Oh, my God. I knew it.  - Who's first?
- 上帝啊 我懂了  - 谁先来?
- "Who's first"? No.  - We don't want you to kill us.
- "谁先来"? 错了  - 我们不是雇你来杀我们
- We want you to kill another person.  - If anyone's first, probably him.
- 雇你杀的是别人  - 谁第一 他吧
No. Goddamn it.
别 去你的
Gentlemen, gentlemen, what are you talking about?
老板们 你们在说什么?
Your ad said you do wet work.
广告上说你做湿身行动
That's correct. I urinate on other men for money.
是啊 我尿在别的男人身上来赚钱
- What was that?  - What'd he say?
- 那是啥?  - 他刚说什么?
I think he said he pisses on dudes.
我听他说尿在别人身上
Why else do you think my ad was in the "men seeking men" section?
不然你们以为我为啥登广告在"男人寻找男人"(男同)专栏?
Where was it?
什么专栏?
- You fucking idiot.  - Could you be dumber?
- 你个蠢货  - 你还能再蠢不?
- Why look in the "men seeking men"...?  - We are men looking for a man!
- 为什么在 "男人寻找男人"...?  - 我们是几个男人 寻找某个男人啊!
How do people let you work on their teeth?
大家怎么能放心把牙交给你?
They don't, actually. I just hand the tools to Julia.
他们不放心 我只是递手术工具的
Are you telling me that I've driven all this way and nobody wants to get pissed on?
你们意思是 我大老远的开车过来 没人想被我尿喽
Uh-uh. Well, it's not our thing.
我们没那嗜好
Sorry about that.
抱歉了
Can I use your toilet? I stored up rather a large amount of pee for this.
我能用下洗手间吗? 为此我可是憋了无数的尿啊
- Sure. Yeah, it's right through there.  - Knock yourself out.
- 可以 就在那边  - 自便
Oh, and by the way, I still will want my $200.
哦 还有 别忘了200块
- Understandable.  - We insist.
- 可以理解  - 我们会付的
- Two hundred, huh? A bargain.  - To kill three people?
- 200块 哼? 真便宜啊  - 200块杀个人?
- I thought it was such a good deal.  - Dipshit.
- 我原以为这主意不错  - 笨蛋
- Reflects poorly on me that you're my friend.  - Hear what's going on in there?
- 我居然有你这种笨蛋朋友  - 听到尿声了吧?
That was almost all over us.
差点都尿我们身上了
Okay, I'm gonna take the blame on that one.
好吧 刚那事都怪我
- You bet your ass you will.  - You should take the blame, then you buy dinner.
- 他妈不怪你怪谁  - 都是你的错 晚饭你请
- It was an honest mistake.  - That's not how you find a killer.
- 这是老实人会犯的错  - 你居然那样找杀手
- Oh, you know how to find a killer?  - Yeah, I bet I...
- 你知道该怎么找杀手?  - 是的 我敢赌...
Yeah, hey, you know what? Yeah. I got an idea.
你知道吗? 我有主意了
What are you doing?
你在干吗?
你干吗呢?
Good evening, Mr.Buckman.
Buckman先生 晚上好
Thank you for contacting Nav Guide. My name is Gregory.
欢迎使用导航指南 我是Gregory
How may I be of service this evening?
今晚如何为您效劳?
Yeah, me and my buddy are looking for the most dangerous bar in the city. Can you help us, please?
我和兄弟们正在找城里最刺激的酒吧 请帮帮我们
- We're going to dinner.  - I'm sorry?
- 我们要去吃饭了  - 请再说一遍
Looking for a bar filled with criminals. Lowlife thugs, hard-core shitheads.
我们找那种里面都是罪犯 底层恶棍 蠢蛋 的酒吧
- What do you got for us?  - Let's go to a restaurant.
- 有什么建议?  - 去饭店吧
I'm afraid our listings are not organized by danger, sir.
抱歉搜索栏里没有刺激 这个词
I see there's an Applebee's three blocks from your location.
不过离你的位置三个街区 有个苹果蜂蜜酒吧
- Perfect.  - No, not really helpful.
- 完美  - 没用
They're not the kind of shitheads we need. Anything else?
我们找的不是这种鸟地方 还有啥?
I could direct you to a neighborhood...
我可以指引你们到附近...
with the greatest number of carjackings.
劫车案高发地
- Now we're thinking outside the box.  - I wanna go to dinner.
- 现在有点意思了  - 我要吃饭
- I Love it.  - That's probably right.
- 就去那里  - 应该没错
Very good, Sir. You may wish to lock your doors.
很好 先生 到时候您最好别忘了锁上车门
- This is worse than getting pissed on.  - Shh.
- 这个要比尿我身上还要坏  - 嘘
- I'd rather be pissed on.  - Jesus.
- 我宁愿被尿在身上  - 天啊
You weren't kidding, Gregory. This is, uh, a bad part of town.
你果然没开玩笑 Gregory 这条街果然很阴森
Yeah, if in case, you can stay on the line. You're still there?
就是 以防万一 你要保持通话啊 你还在吗?
- I'm still here, Sir.  -Just keep, uh, keep us on the line.
- 我一直在线的 先生  - 嗯 和我们保持联系就行
I'm always curious about these things, but is your real name Gregory?
我其实一直很好奇 你真的叫做Gregory?
Uh... No, Sir. My real name is Atmanand.
呃... 不是的 先生 我真名叫做Atmanand
How do you get Gregory from that?
那你怎么取了Gregory这个名字?
Oh. Gregory was assigned to me by Nav Guide.
哦 Gregory是Nav导航公司发给我的名字
Why not let you use your real name?
他们为什么不让你用真名啊?
They say many Americans find our real names hard to pronounce.
他们说 很多美国人觉得我们的真名发音很拗口
Hey, you know what? I'm not gonna play by their rules anymore.
嘿 你知道吗? 我不用守你们公司的规矩
- From now on, I'm gonna call you Ahmenan.  - Ya.
- 现在开始 我就叫你Ahmenan  - 就是
- Atmanand.  - What is it?
- 是Atmanand  - 是什么来着?
- Ammenand.  - Atmanad.
- 是叫Ammenand  - 应该是Atmanad
- Atmanand.  - Atmanand.
- 应该是Atmanand  - 是Atmanand
I'm gonna call you Gregory, that name's fucking a nightmare, buddy.
我还是叫你Gregory吧 伙计 你的名字他妈就是个悲剧
- Hey, baby.  - Oh, boy.
- 嘿 宝贝  - 哦 天啊
- You hurt his feelings.  - I didn't hurt anything.
- 你伤了他的心了  - 我才没有
You have arrived at your destination, Sir.
你已经到达你的目的地了 先生
- All right. Well, thanks, Gregory.  - You're welcome.
- 好的 谢谢啦 Gregory  - 不用谢
All right. All right, here we go.
很好 就要这样的 我们来了
- This is a really bad idea.  - No, this is a great idea.
- 这个办法可真不太好啊  - 不对 这个办法好极了
- Are you just gonna yell "anybody here kill for money"?  - No.
- 你就打算直接喊"有没有人靠杀人赚钱的"吗?  - 才不是
- That's a terrible plan. - Follow me. I got this.
- 这个计划太烂了  - 跟我来 看我的
Where you going? I don't feel we should stay.
你要去哪里? 我觉得我们不应该留在这里
All right.
好吧
- Bowflex?  - Shut up.
- 够壮啊?  - 滚
Hola.
你好
Ah.
哈
My man.
老弟
Hey, uh, does anyone here kill people for money?
嘿 这里有没有人靠杀人赚钱的啊?
- Kurt.  - The fuck you just say?
- Kurt  - 你他妈刚刚说什么?
No, it's not a race thing.
不是 这和种族没有关系
Uh, I believe that society discriminates and disenfranchises you folks.
嗯 我知道你们黑佬受到社会歧视 并被划为下等公民
- "You folks"?  - Subtle.
- "你们黑佬"?  - 情况不妙啊
Man, I'm a small-business owner. Who the hell you calling disenfranchised?
同志 我是个小生意人 你说谁是下等公民啊?
Well, not you in particular, in that instance.
好吧 这句话 不是特别指你的
Oh, right. You mean all black people.
哦 好吧 那你就是指所有黑人啦
- Yes.  - No.
- 是的  - 不是
- I'm gonna be in the car.  - Oh, a baseball bat.
- 我回车里去  - 他抄家伙了
Uh, I didn't mean to offend you. I'm sorry if that's what happened, okay?
哦 我不是有意冒犯你的 如果有冒犯的地方 我道歉 行吗?
If... if you know me better, you know my heart's in the right place.
如... 如果你了解我的话 你知道我的心脏在正确的位置(指没有恶意)
In five seconds, your heart gonna be in the wrong place.
给你五秒快滚 不然你心脏就要被移位了
- Four, three, two, let's roll. - Got it. Okay. Take care.
- 四 三 二 我们还是走吧  - 了解 再见啊
Have a nice day. Good day to you.
玩的开心点啊 玩的开心点
Bye, baby.
拜拜 宝贝
Don't say a word. I know, I know.
什么都别说 我知道 我懂的
Hit the button. Hit the button.
开车门吧 开车门
- Guys, I don't know. Should we quit?  - Yeah, definitely.
- 伙计们 我们要不要放弃啊?  - 要啊 肯定要
- Yo. Think I can help you boys. - Is that for us?
- 哎 我想我可以帮你们  - 是在和我们说话吗?
- Here we go. - Not interested, thank you.
- 这就来  - 没什么兴趣 多谢啦
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Ah... let's follow a strange guy into a dark corner.
啊... 要跟陌生人去个黑暗的角落了
Somebody said y'all looking for somebody to help with business.
有人告诉我 你们要找人帮忙办点事?
-  Yep.  - Well, um...
- 是的  - 嗯...
- are you a businessman?  - Yeah.
- 你是个生意人吗?  - 是的
Motherfucker Jones.
我是Motherfucker Jones
- How's that? - Motherfucker Jones.
- 怎么说?  - 我叫Motherfucker Jones
Your first name is "Motherfucker"?
你名字叫"Motherfucker"?
Last name Jones. You got a problem with that?
我就姓Jones 你有意见吗?
No. No. Cool name. Yeah. Is that, like, on your birth certificate too?
没有 没有 好名字 身份证上也是这名字?
No, goofball.
不是的 白痴
My real name is Dean.
我真名叫做Dean
Dean Jones. Same name of the actor in "Herbie, the Love Bug".
Dean Jones 和"万能金龟车"里的演员同名啊
Yeah, he won't know who that is.
别逗了 他怎么会看迪士尼电影
- I know who he is, bitch. - Sorry.
- 我知道那个演员 贱人  - 对不起
I can't walk around in this fucking neighborhood with that Disney-ass name.
我可不能用娘们的名字在这片地方混饭吃
How'd you get the name Motherfucker?
你怎么会有Motherfucker这个名字的?
When I was a kid, I snuck into my mother's bedroom.
我还是个小孩子的时候 我溜进了我妈的卧室
Ooh.  Uh-oh.
哦 啊哦
- She was laying there naked. - Dean.
- 她就裸着躺在那里  - Dean
- She had been drinking all night. - We get it.
- 她整晚都在喝酒  - 我们懂了
- And then I snuck up behind her,  - Ah...
- 接着我溜到她身后  - 啊...
- and then I slipped my fingers...  - hum...
- 接着我把手指伸进...  - 呵...
- into her purse.  - Purse? He said "purse."
- 她的钱包  - 钱包? 他是说"钱包"
I took her money, the whole week's pay. I really fucked her over.
我拿走了她一周的薪水 伤了她的心(英语表达为fuck over)
And that's how I got the name Motherfucker Jones.
我就是因为这个 被叫做Motherfucker Jones
- Right  - Yeah
- 这样啊  - 哦
They should call you Motherfucker-Over Jones to avoid confusion.
他们应该叫你Motherfucker-Over Jones 这样就没有误会了
- What's the confusion?  - There's no confusion.
- 有什么好误会的?  - 没什么好误会的
Here we go. We're gonna get back on track here. Sir, we each have a boss, uh...
我们还是说正经事吧 先生 我们每人都有个老板 呃...
that, you know...
那种 你懂的...
There's three bosses, and it would be best if those bosses maybe were no longer....
一共三个老板 如果这些老板人间蒸发的话...
- No longer around anymore.  - We want them...
- 就最好不过了  - 我们想要他们...
- You know?  - killed.
- 你懂吗?  - 死掉
You got the cheese?
你们有票子吗?
We got the cheese. What kind of cheese are you thinking?
我们有票子 你想要哪种票子?
- What is that, three hits?  - Yeah.
- 怎么说 就三个人?  - 是的
- Mmm... Thirty large.  - Whoa.
- 呃... 3万块  - 哇哦
- Hungry.  - That's a lot of cheese.
- 好凶哦  - 要好多票子啊
Oh, here's an idea.
哦 要不这样
If you kill two, could we get the third one hold the cheese?
如果你杀掉两个 第三个能够免费吗?
It's no negotiations. Thirty large or nothing.
这不是在谈判 要么三万块要么就不干
- That's more cheese than we've got.  - Okay, then. It's five large now.
- 我们可没有这么多票子  - 给你们打个折 五千
- Then we're in. We're in. - In, we're in.
- 这样的话 我们做了  - 做了 我们做了
Hang on. Wouldn't it be awful if it was traceable back to us?
等一下 如果这件事追查到我们身上不就糟了啊?
I don't even know your names.
我甚至都不知道你叫什么
- That is rude. This is Dale. - Don't say my name.
- 这的确不礼貌 这是Dale  - 不要叫我的名字
- He means he...  - Shut the fuck up.
- 他的意思是...  - 给我他妈的闭嘴
Listen. Bring the money here tomorrow, I'll take care of the rest.
听着 明天带钱来这里就行 其他的我会摆平的
Do you want it in something specific, a shoebox, duffel bag?
你想要用什么特定的东西装嘛 鞋盒或者行李箱?
- Just be here with the fucking money.  - Yeah.
- 他妈的带钱来就行了  - 好的
- Put it in a briefcase.  - Thanks for your time.
- 放在公文包就行  - 多谢啦
Here we go.
我们走
Is the briefcase coming out of your end?
公文包你搞定吗?
Looks like it's all there.
看起来都在这里了
Didn't even need a briefcase. It's a small stack.
这根本就不用行李箱 这只有一小叠
- We should have used a manila envelope. - It's all right.
- 我们可以用牛皮信封包的  - 没关系
What is your projected outside date of completion, Motherfucker?
你什么时候可以干掉他们 Motherfucker?
Ah...
啊...
I just got back from doing a dime for some real nasty shit.
我早年犯了些事 蹲了10年大牢 刚放出来
- That's 10 years.  - I know.
- 哇10年  - 我知道的
They're looking at me. I'm on probation, and if I step out of line...
警局在监视着我 我还在缓刑期中 如果我一轻举妄动...
I'm going back.
我就会被送回去
- Right.  - Understood.
- 是的  - 理解
- Period? End of story?  - What does that mean?
- 结束了? 故事就讲完了?  - 这算什么意思?
- Wait. You said you'd take care of this. - Yeah, I'll take care of it.
- 等一下 你说你会摆平剩下的事情的  - 是啊 我会摆平的
I'm gonna be your murder consultant.
我将是你们的谋杀顾问
I'm sorry, but, uh....
不好意思 但是 嗯...
- No, man. Right? That's not cool. - You don't shut this fucking hamster up....
- 不对啊 伙计 这样不地道啊  - 你们他妈的不能让这碎嘴小老鼠闭嘴...
- Don't call me a hamster now. Come on.  - Easy, easy.
- 拜托 别叫我碎嘴小老鼠  - 冷静 冷静
- No, it's just upsetting.  - No, it's... it's somewhat accurate.
- 没事 只是有点生气而已  - 你是有些... 像碎嘴小老鼠
Look, that is not what we talked about, Motherfucker.
听着 我们不是请你来当顾问的 Motherfucker
So how about we just take the money and we'll get out of here?
所以要不然我们就拿着钱直接走人算了?
How about you go fuck yourself? No refunds.
你怎么不去自己干自己啊? 概不退款
That's $5000. If you think we're just gonna walk out and let you keep that...
那可是5000美金  你以为这么容易就能拿到...
- I think you're forgetting...  - Okay, don't go grabbing quickly.
- 那就问问我的枪吧...  - 行 别这么快就掏家伙啊
Jesus.
天啊
Mr. Motherfucker, please, don't shoot us. Let's just talk it out.
Motherfucker先生 求你了 别开枪 有话好好说
Listen, $5000 is mine. I don't care what you say.
听着 5000美金是我的了 我不管你们怎么说
You can take my advice or get the fuck out of here.
你们要么听我的建议 要么就他妈的滚出这里
- That's a terrible deal.  - We should listen to him.
- 这个主意太糟了  - 我们还是听他的吧
- Okay, $5000 worth of advice?  - Yeah.
- 好吧 值5000美金的建议  - 是啊
Most killers are first-timers.
大多人杀人都是第一次
You wanna pull off a brilliant murder, you gotta act like it's an accident.
你想要完美的杀掉一个人 你就要把它弄成像是个意外
Failed brakes, gas leaks, suicide.
刹车失灵 煤气泄漏 自杀
You do it right, you ain't even gotta be there when it goes down.
如果你做的好的话 他死的时候 你甚至不用在现场
Oh, boy. That's five grand worth, huh?
哦 伙计 这样就值五千美金了 啊?
- Pretty pedestrian. - Not really. Obvious information, isn't it?
- 很业余啊  - 不是吧 这些人人都懂啊?
Sounds like Scooby-Doo. How are we supposed to fake three accidents?
听起来像是空手套白狼啊 我们要怎么样才能伪造三场意外呢?
You stalk your prey.
你们要观察你们的目标
Gotta be smart. Find out where they live,
动点脑子 搞清楚他们住哪里
find out their habits. What's their hobbies.
有什么习惯 有什么兴趣
What they like, what food they like, who they fucking.
他们喜欢干什么 吃什么 干过谁
- Word.  - Find them vulnerable.
- 脏话啊  - 找到他们的弱点
I have a job, you know! What's that, surveillance and recon?
你要知道 我有工作的! 哪有闲功夫监视还有侦查?
That's why we were hiring, because we wanna sub that out. We have jobs.
这就是为什么我们要找你 得有人帮我们做这些事 我们得工作啊
Even if you pull it off perfectly...
就算你们做的天衣无缝...
if you crackers got motives...
只要你们有作案动机的话...
the popo...
这些黑皮...
- That's police.  - will pin it to you.
- 就是警察  - 会查到你们的
We all have clear motives for killing our bosses...
我们都有明显的谋杀老板的动机...
so this is not gonna work. This is garbage.
所以这个行不通的 全是废话
I got it.
我懂了
Why don't you kill each other's bosses?
要不你们杀掉对方的老板?
- That's actually a good idea.  - It's not bad.
- 这的确是个好想法  - 想法不错
Yeah, like "Hitchcock's Strangers on a Train", right?
对啊 就像"火车怪客"里面一样 对吧?
- I didn't see that. They do that?  - Danny DeVito movie. It's funny.
- 我没看过 他们这么做的?  - Danny DeVito的电影 可搞笑了
That famous Alfred Hitchcock, Danny DeVito movie. That's the one he's...
那个著名的Alfred Hitchcock Danny DeVito的电影 他就凭这个...
- Come on.  - What?
- 拜托  - 干嘛?
Come on, you're thinking of "Throw Momma From the Train".
拜托 你在想的是"谋杀老妈"
- That's what it is. - That I saw.
- 原来它叫这个名字  - 这本我看过
Good movie. That's what you're thinking about.
电影不错 这才是你想要的
It's the same idea, though. We kill each other's bosses, there's no link to us.
这两个想法是一致的 我们杀掉对方的老板 就能洗掉嫌疑了
Exactly. Five thousand dollars well spent, right?
就是这样 五千美金花地很值 对吧?
- No, not at all.  - Waste of money.
- 不值 一点也不值  - 打水漂了
Well, too fucking bad.
太他妈糟糕了
Get out.
滚吧
Hello.
你好
Hey. I'm outside. You ready to do a little recon?
嘿 我在外面了 你准备好去做点小侦查了吗?
Yep. Yeah. I have to get Harken to let me leave a little bit early.
好了 准备好了 我得设法让Harken放我早点走
Why? What's the difference? Not like he'll be your boss much longer.
为什么啊? 有什么区别? 他做老板又不会太长时间了
I'll be down in three minutes.
我三分钟后就下来
Three minutes it is. Bye. He'll be down in three minutes.
那就三分钟 白白 他三分钟就能下来了
- Dude, these seats are crazy comfortable. Right? - Oh. I know, I know. Ah...
- 伙计 这椅子超舒服的 对吧?  - 哦 我知道 爽啊...
The worst report I have ever read in my life, you nimwit.
我一辈子见过最烂得报告 你个废材
You're such a fucking dweeb.
你就他妈是个蠢蛋
Do you have a parking space? Because I'm gonna take it away from you.
你有停车位吗? 我要取消你使用停车位的资格
Who is it, like your mother-in-law that knows my wife?
到底是谁 你岳母认识我的老婆?
How you got this fucking job, I don't even understand.
你他妈怎么找到这个工作的 我甚至有点想不通了
Ugh.
呕
What the hell?
见什么鬼了?
Sorry, everybody. I've been fighting that bug all day. Let me get back to work.
大家不好意思啊 我已经被这病折磨整天了 我现在就回去工作
No, no, no. You're disgusting. Go home. I don't want you getting anyone else sick.
别 别 别 你个恶心鬼 滚回家吧 我可不想你把病传染给其他人
Probably best.
这样估计最好
Take all your work with you and have it on my desk 6 a.m. Monday.
带上你要做的东西 礼拜一早上6点做好放在我桌子上
- You got it. Thank you, Mr. Harken.  - Jesus Christ.
- 我知道了 谢谢了 Harken先生  - 老天爷啊
- Don't forget to take your fucking trash can.  - Yeah, that's mine.
- 别忘了带上你恶心的垃圾桶  - 知道了 我会带走的
You goddamn barfing pig.
你个天杀的
Evens are over here.
双号门牌在那边
I know, but sometimes on some streets evens are on the opposite side.
我知道 但是有些街道双号门牌在另外一边
Never.
不可能
Never have and they never will. There it is, 428.
这不可能有 也不会有 就那里 428号
- Which one, which one?  - Don't stop right in front of it.
- 哪个 哪个?  - 别直接停前面啊
Stop right here. Right here, right here.
就停那里 那里 那里
Okay, boys.
好了 伙计们
We wait till Pellit makes a move, then we tail him, all right.
等到Pellit出门 我们就跟踪他 就这样定了
- It is on like "Donkey Kong".  - Ha, ha.
- 这就像是在玩"大金刚游戏"  - 哈哈
- Hells yeah, man.  - Here we go, huh?
- 太他妈像了 伙计  - 那就行动呗 对吧?
I'm fucking pumped.
我太他妈激动了
Oh, my God. This sucks.
哦 老天啊 这太烂了吧
This is horrible, man.
这太可怕了 伙计
Are we even sure this guy's home?
他倒底在家嘛?
- Let's go check this out.  - Yeah, we should probably look, right?
- 我们去看一下  - 对啊 我们应该去看一下 对吧?
Shh.
嘘
Oh, my God.
哦 老天啊
All right, what do you wanna do? What's the plan?
好了 你们想怎么做? 有什么计划吗?
- Let's look through this window right here.
- 我们就从那边窗户往里面望
No, no. No, let's ring the bell. If we hear any movement...
不行 不行 我们按门铃 要是听到任何动静的话...
You're not gonna ring the bell. Look through the window right here.
你可别去按门铃 从那边窗户往里偷看好了
- No, it's no a bad idea.  - Right here.
- 不会啊 这个建议不错啊  - 这边
Dude, chances are, he's not home. I haven't seen any activity in this house since...
伙计 他很有可能不在家 我来了之后就没有看到这房子里面有什么动静...
What are you doing? You're not gonna ring the doorbell.
你们在干什么? 你们别去按门铃
Whoo-hoo!
哇哦 哇哦!
- Come on. Come on. Dale, Dale,Dale.
- 快点 快点 Dale Dale Dale
I didn't make it in.
我没赶上
I'm sorry, guys. Didn't make it in.
伙计们 对不住啊 没赶上
You in?
你进来了?
Yeah, I'm Okay. Jesus Christ, the guy owns a fucking bear?
进来了 没事了 老天啊 这个人他妈有头熊?
- We're breaking and entering here.  - I know. Shh. Oh, look at this.
- 我们这是非法入侵  - 我知道 轻点 看看这地方
Look at this place. It's awful. It's like a douchebag museum.
看看这地方 这太可怕了 这里就像是个废品博物馆
It's like we stepped inside the mind of an asshole.
我们就像闯进了一个疯子的大脑
Shit. He's got a foosball table.
我操 他有张桌上足球
Dale! Don't touch anything. Get your hands off that.
Dale! 别碰任何东西 把手拿远点
- Fingerprints.  - Yeah, fingerprints.
- 会留下指纹  - 没错 指纹
- God. We should be wearing gloves.  We don't have  - Oh, here. I know.
- 上帝 我们应该戴手套的 但我们没有  - 哦 有了 我知道
Use your sleeves. Use your sleeves.
用你的袖子 用你的袖子
- For what?  - Use them for gloves.
- 用来干嘛?  - 当手套啊
- Come on.  - I can see my fingerprints from here. This is no good.
- 拜托  - 我看到我的指纹已经留在这里了
这可不妙啊
- What do we do? What's the plan?  - We're here to get some intel.
- 怎么办? 有什么计划吗?  - 我们来这里收报
- "Intel"?  - It's short for "intelligence."
- "报"?  - "情报"的简称
- I know what it stands for.  - Then why did you ask?
- 我知道是什么意思  - 那你为什么问?
Why are we talking about this? Let's split up.
我们为什么要讨论这些? 分头行动吧
In and out, in and out. We'll find something good, and we're in and out of here.
里面找找外面找找 我们会找到好东西的 我们到处找找
- Stop chatting and start looking. -We're committing a crime. This is a crime.
- 别瞎扯了 快找  - 我们在犯罪 会被抓的
Whoa.
哇哦
- Nick.  - Yeah?
- Nick 快看  - 什么?
- Now, this would count as intel, right?  - Holy shit, that's a lot of cocaine.
- 这算是一个情报了 是吧?  - 该死 这么多可卡因
Have you ever seen this much cocaine?
你看到过这么多可卡因吗?
That's gotta be worth, what, 10, 15,000?
这可能值一万? 一万五?
Oh, I blew it. I blew that, didn't I?
哦 我搞砸了 我搞砸了 对吗?
Hmm.
呃
- Don't inhale.  -Grab the box. I'll scoop it in.
- 别吸气  - 抓住盒子 我来掏
I really don't wanna touch it. I don't have sleeve-gloves.
我真的不想碰它 我没有袖袖手套
Get something to...Ugh. I'll scoop it in.
找些东西去 呃 我来掏
So bitter.
真可怜
Hmm.
嗯
In the butt you go, go, go.
搓屁屁呀 搓搓搓
There you go.
完事儿了
Big scoop.
多掏点
All right, let me try this. Look out.
试试这个 小心
- Yeah, that better work.  - Watch out.
- 太好了 这个好用  - 小心
There you go.
搞定了
- I don't know.  - Go slow.
- 还不知道呢  - 得慢慢地
Get on the couch. Stop helping.
坐沙发上去 别帮倒忙了
All right.
好嘞
In you go.
搓搓搓
Ooh.
哦
You probably should have emptied the DustBuster first.
你也许应该先清理下吸尘器
Is that what you think?
你真的这么想吗?
I was thinking that. On account of the dust.
我本来是想 看到有这么多灰 还是算了吧
Well, I've heard of butt floss, but this is ridiculous. Ha, ha.
我听说过清理屁屁的牙线 但这真可笑 哈哈
- Get a sifter, or a... - Colander.
- 找个筛子 或者... - 滤网
Colander would be good.
滤网不错
And I'll start picking.
我要开始挑了
That'll do.
搞定了
I feel like everything'll work out. Cause I'm like a machine. Look how fast I am.
我感觉所有事都可以解决 我就像个机器 看我多快
I'm moving super fast. I can't even feel my nose.
我在快速移动 我感觉不到我的鼻子了
Wanna know what's weird? I should be panicking...
想知道我的感受吗? 我应该感到恐慌的
and I am a little, but it's in a very good way.
我确实有一点 但总体情况不坏
It's a good kind of panic because I feel like I wanna die...
这是一种很舒服的恐慌 就像是要上天堂了一样...
- but I also feel very, very, very good. - Yeah.
- 但我又觉得非常非常不错  - 没错
Hey! What are you guys doing?
嘿! 你们在干嘛?
Nothing. But before we go, I wanna take one more dump.
没什么 但在我们走前 我想再上个大号
Take a dump and I'm gonna do push-ups. Because I gotta get fit.
你上大号 我再做个俯卧撑 因为我想练个好身材
What the hell have you guys done?
你们究竟干了什么?
I'm feeling good, dude. Wanna help me clean?
我感觉很棒 伙计 想帮我打扫一下吗?
We bond over this. This is friendship stuff.
我们老交情了 这是朋友该做的事
We broke into someone's house. It's the most amazing experience of my life.
我们闯进别人家里 这是我人生中最疯狂的经历了
We broke into a man's house. Suddenly, I'm like an expert at sifting cocaine.
我们闯进别人家里 突然 我变成了一个筛选可卡因的专家
It's amazing. Come here and help me with this.
太震惊了 过来帮帮我
Can't believe we weren't prepared.
真不敢相信我们还没准备好就行动了
That was completely dangerous, a total waste of time.
太危险了 完全是浪费时间
Well, no. Actually, not a total waste of time. Look what I got.
不 事实上 不完全是浪费时间 看我拿到了什么
- Not bad, huh?  - What is that?
- 还不错吧?  - 那是什么?
- Is this his phone?  - That's his phone.
- 这是他的手机吗?  - 对 是他的手机
- You steal this?  - I sure did.
- 你偷的?  - 没错
- It's got his contacts, schedule.  - Very nice.
- 里面有他的联系人 行程表  - 很好
- No.  - What do you mean, "no"?
- 不  - 你说"不"是什么意思?
That's a crime. Pfft. Nope. Ha. No one said we'd be stealing.
那是犯罪 不 哈 之前可没说要偷东西
- This is a good grab.  - We broke in! You guys did cocaine!
- 这是个好东西  - 我们非法入侵! 你们还吸粉
!
- Right. Two,three crimes.  - He's all jitzed out. Ignore him.
- 对 两个 总共三个罪行  - 他抽了 别管他
We're in the process of getting ready to kill three people...
我们正实施谋杀三人的计划...
and you're giving me shit about stealing a phone?
你却怪我偷了个电话?
Run it by me if you'll be stealing stuff.
你要偷东西的话应该让我去
- Run it by you?  - Run it by me!
- 让你去?  - 让我去!
- Nick, will you hold this for a second?  - What are you doing?
- Nick 你可以帮我开一下车吗?  - 你想干嘛?
"Run"? I'm not gonna run anything by you.
"让你去"? 我不会让你办任何事的
I'm not gonna run anything by you. Dickhead.
我不会让你办任何事的 傻瓜
- There's a lot of stuff in here.  - I know.
- 这里面涉及了很多事  - 我知道
- Wanna go check out your boss now?  - Yeah, I guess we should.
- 现在该查你老板了吧?  - 是的 我也这么想
- You don't punch the driver!  - You don't punch the fucking driver.
- 你不能打司机!  - 狗日的司机是不能打的
I'm coked out of my fucking brain. I'll punch whoever the fuck I want to.
我吸上脑了 我想打谁就打谁
Let's do this, guys. Feeling good.
来吧 伙计 感觉真棒
- Be very quiet out there.  - Calm down, Dale.
- 待那里安静点  - 冷静 Dale
You know what? Hang on a second.
知道吗? 先听我说
Dale? Dude, hold it. Last time the three of us did this, it was very messy.
Dale? 伙计们 等等 上次我们三个行动的的时候 完全是乱来
- It was awesome, exciting. - It was clunky as hell.
- 爽翻了 真兴奋  - 糟糕透了
Here's what we'll do. In the event that Harken is not here, just me and Kurt go in.
我们现在要做的是 如果Harken不在 就我和Kurt进去
You'll stay out here, not go in, and be our lookout.
你待在这里 别进去 帮我们把风
What? Are you kidding me? That's awesome. I love that. The lookout.
什么? 你耍我吗? 爽翻了 我喜欢 把风
- I don't know what the guy looks like though.  - Doesn't matter.
- 可我不知道他长什么样  - 没关系
You see anybody, just assume that it's Harken, send us a signal.
你看到任何人 都把他当做Harken 给我们一个信号
- Okay? Have a seat.  - Okay.
- 好吗? 坐下  - 好的
Okay. Send a... I'm gonna honk the horn six times.
好的 发信号.. 我按六次喇叭
- Goddamn it. No.  - Did he say "six"?
- 该死 不  - 你说"六次"?
- Something much more subtle.  - That's too many.
- 你得动静小些  - 六次太多了
- More subtle? Four honks?  - Can you honk once?
- 动静小些? 四次?  - 你可以只按一次吗?
- Are you kidding?  - Not at all.
- 你开玩笑?  - 我说真的
People honk once all the time. You'll be in and out.
如果你们听到一次喇叭就出来 不是要进进出出
- We'll know it's you.  - Come on, man. Dale, two honks.
- 我们会知道哪个是你按的  - 好吧 伙计 按两下
- That kind of tone's gonna get you nowhere.  - All right, two honks.
- 按一次肯定没用  - 好吧 两下喇叭
- Just two honks. A little tap, tap.  - Okay.
- 只按两下 轻轻地  - 好
Two very long, very slow honks.
两声又长又响的喇叭
- I'm gonna check this window over here.  - Okay.
- 我去看看那个窗  - 好
- There's nothing on that side.  -Yeah. I don't think there's anyone in there.
- 那边没动静  - 太好了 我想里面没有人
I think he's definitely out.
我想他肯定出去了
Maybe we can find a way in upstairs.
可能我们能想个办法上楼
Yeah, or maybe there's a window open.
没错 可能有个窗开着
Or better yet....
或者最好
That makes things easier, huh?
这样更简单 呃?
I like the way you think. Move.
我喜欢你这法子 走开
- No, don't do that. Hey! God!  - Oh, shit.
- 不 别这么干 上帝!  - 哦 该死
I broke a rock.
我把石头砸烂了
Please tell me you realize that was a key thing.
别告诉我你不知道里面藏着钥匙
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
哦 对 对 对
You weren't gonna throw a rock through the door?
你不是想用石头砸开门吧?
No, of course not. No, I wanted to open it.
不 当然不 我只想打开门
Like a real cat burglar.
像一个真正的飞天贼
Wow.
喔
Just recon, now, okay?
先侦查下 好吗?
- Hey, take this.  - I don't want it. I want my hands free.
- 嘿 拿着这个  - 我不要 我想空着手
You broke it.
是你打烂的
I feel the intel...
我感到有情报
- God!  - Okay, just a cat.
- 天哪!  - 好吧 只是一只猫
Out of nowhere.
突然就钻出来了
Just a cat. We're all right. Let's look upstairs. Come on.
只是一只猫 没事的 我们上楼看看 来吧
They call me hell.
他们叫我混蛋
They call me Stacey.
他们叫我Stacey
That's not my name. That's not my name.
这不是我的名字 这不是我的名字
They call me hell.
他们叫我混蛋
They call me her.
They call me hell.
他们叫我混蛋
They call me Stacey.
他们叫我Stacey
That's not my name. That's not my name.
这不是我的名字 这不是我的名字
Oh! Goddamn it.
哦! 该死
Jesus, how many cats do they have?
该死 他们养了几只猫?
- It's the same one, I think. Yeah.  - Really?
- 我觉得是同一只  - 真的么?
Quick little bugger, huh?
快闪的小家伙 嗯?
Hey.
嘿
- Shit, is that Harken's wife?  - Yeah, that's her.
- 该死 那是Harken的老婆?  - 没错 是她
- Oh, man, she is hot.  - She sure is. Here we go.
- 哦 伙计 她真辣  - 是啊 我们走
I'd like to bend her over a barrel and show her the 50 states.
我真想把她弯下 干得她满头星
- I don't know what that means.  - Ah, it's a saying.
- 我不知道你在说什么  - 是人都知道
- I don't think so. - No, it is, it is. Yeah. No, people say that.
- 我不这么认为  - 是的 没错 大家都这么说
- I haven't heard it.  - I've definitely heard people say that.
- 我没听过  - 我肯定有人这么说过
I'm not gonna argue. Let's continue the recon.
我不跟你争了 我们继续侦查吧
- Well, it's definitely a phrase.  - It sure isn't.
- 那是个习语  - 才不是呢
Yeah, it is. It's from a book. The Great Gatsby, maybe?
它就是 有本书上这么写的 可能是"了不起的盖茨比"?
Let's just look for an address book or a day planner or something. You know?
我们去找找他的电话本或行程表什么的 行不?
You know, it's too bad we're not looking for cats. These people fucking love cats.
知道吗 我们不找猫真是可惜 这家人看来超喜欢猫
Hey, schmuck face.
嘿 蠢蛋
You wanna tell me what you're doing littering on my street?
你想告诉我为什么你在我的街上扔垃圾吗?
I think what happened, ahem, was that the wind blew it out of my hand.
我想是因为 风吹过我的手的关系
I don't care if the wind blew it out of your twat.
我才不管是不是风吹过你的手毛
Why don't you take this piece-of-shit car and get off my fucking block.
为什么你不开着你的破车离开我的街区
I don't know why you're mad at the car. I don't think we should get hostile now.
我不知道为什么你看我的车不爽 我觉得我们不应该敌对
"Hostile"? You wanna see hostile?
"敌对"? 你想看什么是敌对吗?
How about I go in my house and I get my...?
要不要我进屋拿个...?
What are? What's going on with you?
拿个什么? 你怎么了?
Peanuts.
花生
"Penis"?
"鸡鸡"?
Oh, peanuts.
哦 花生
That was a peanut butter sandwich. Are you not good with peanuts?
那是花生酱三明治 你对花生过敏?
What are you pointing at? What's going on? What's here?
你在指什么? 怎么了? 这里有什么?
Oh, I got it! What do I do? What do I do?
哦 我拿到了! 然后呢? 该怎么做?
"Check the needle, pump back, pump..." Okay, hold on. I'm a slow reader.
"检查针头 拉开 拉..." 好的 等等 我有轻微阅读障碍
"Hold the pump..." Okay, okay!
"拉那个..." 行了 行了!
Jab it in your chest. Okay. I got you, dude. Ready?
戳进你的胸口 好的 我搞定啦 伙计 准备好了?
How you feeling, you good?
感觉怎么样 好点了吗?
You good? Did I get you? Did I get you?
你好点了吗? 我插对了吗? 我插对了吗?
Whoa. Whoa. Dude, come here. Hurry.
喔 喔 伙计 过来 快
Look at this.
快看这里
- Is that Harken? Dale's killing Harken?  - That's Harken?
- 那是Harken吗? Dale要杀了Harken?  - 那是Harken吗?
I'm gonna hit you again, okay?
我再来一次 好吗?
- What is he doing?  - He's really doing it?
- 他在干什么?  - 他真的动手了?
- This is the recon stage.  - Holy shit.
- 我们还只是在侦查阶段  - 该死
We gotta get out of here. Come on, we gotta go. Oh, God.
我们得离开这里 来吧 快闪 哦 天哪
I'm pushing on it. Okay.
我在按 好了
What about little jabs? Little jabs?
再来点敲击? 敲击?
Do I get your neck?
还是擢你的脖子?
Was that good?
好点了吗?
Come on, man!
坚持住 伙计!
Oh, my God.
哦 天哪
Hey, hey! Come here!
喂 喂 这里!
What's going on? What are you doing? What's happened?
怎么了? 你在干什么? 出什么事了?
I think he's okay! I hit him with this. Do you know him?
我想他应该没事了! 我用这个戳他 你认识他吗?
Of course, he's my husband. Sweetie? Honey? Sweetheart, are you okay?
当然认识 他是我老公 亲爱的? 亲爱的 你还好吗?
- There he is. Hey.  - Ah. What did you do to me?
- 他醒了 嘿  - 啊 你对我做了什么?
I saved you with your thingy. It was incredible.
我用你的针救了你一命 真是难以置信
Oh, my God, sweetie. He saved your life.
哦 天哪 亲爱的 他救了你的命
You saved his life.
你救了他的命
Okay. That's cool.
好了 没什么
- What's with the hugging?  - Saved your life, man!
- 你干嘛抱他?  - 因为我救了你啊!
Oh, sweetie, I am just so grateful that he was here. You could have died.
哦 亲爱的 得好好谢谢他 如果不是他的话 你可能已经死了
- I'm sure you are grateful he's here.  - Yes, I am.
- 你谢得挺到位嘛  - 是啊
- You know this guy?  - No, I don't.
- 你认识他吗?  - 不认识
Are you fucking this guy? What were you doing, waiting to fuck my wife?
你想和他上床吗? 你在干什么 想上我老婆吗?
Dude, I just met your wife. You want your thing back?
伙计 我才刚认识你太太 你想把它拿回去吗?
- You better get out of here.  - No problem.
- 你最好快点滚  - 没问题
Dave. Dave, what are you...? Honey?
Dave Dave 你这是...? 亲爱的?
Honey, you should be thanking this young man. Why are you being so suspicious?
亲爱的 你应该谢谢这个年轻人 为什么你总是疑神疑鬼的?
Why? You know why I'm being suspicious.
为什么? 你知道我为什么老是疑神疑鬼
Because I know you sleep around on me.
因为我知道你总是背着我偷人
That's ridiculous.
真是不可理喻
What about the way you look at Maurilio?
你看Maurilio的时候是什么眼神?
You realize we're all going to jail because of that idiot?
你觉得我们会因为那个傻瓜进监狱吗?
Man, I can't go to jail. Look at me. I'll get raped like crazy.
伙计 我可不想进监狱 看看我 我会被搞惨的
Fuck, me too.
该死 我也是
Yeah, totally.
对 肯定是这样
I'd get raped just as much as you would, Kurt.
我会被搞得和你一样惨的 Kurt
- Do you think you're more rape-able?  - I'm not saying that.
- 你觉得自己会被搞得更多?  - 我可没什么说
- You're pretty close to saying...  - Oh, fuck.
- 你就是这意思...  - 哦 该死
Holy shit. Did you guys see me out there?
太帅了 你们刚才看见我了吗?
Yeah, we saw you, Dale.
是的 我们看见你了 Dale
Shh. Yeah, we saw that.
嘘 没错 我们看见了
How cool was that?
很厉害吧?
It wasn't cool at all. We come out to gather information...
一点也不 我们是来这里收集情报的
and you start stabbing Harken to death in front of the neighborhood?
你却在大街上活活把Harken捅死了?
- That is Harken?  - Who'd you think you were stabbing?
- 那个人就是Harken?  - 那你以为你捅的人是谁?
I wasn't stabbing anyone.
我谁都没有捅啊
He had an allergic reaction to some peanuts
他闻到花生 起了过敏反应
and I rescued him, know what I mean?
我救了他 你听懂我的意思了吗?
He had a little allergy shot on him and I...
他身上带着小型的防过敏针筒 我就...
I mean, I jabbed him with that, but I was just saving his life.
我就用那个针筒用力戳他 但我是在救他的命
- Saved a man's life.  - Hang on a second.
- 救了那个人一命  - 等一下
So my boss, who we're thinking about planning to kill...
所以我老板 那个我们打算杀掉的人...
is dying in front of you and you saved his life?
就要死在你面前了 而你去求了他一命?
Well, that sounds bad when you say it like that.
你要是这么说的话 听起来的确蛮糟糕的
- Can you open the door?  - That's not cool.
- 你能开下车门吗?  - 这样一点也不地道
- But I didn't know it was Harken.  - Hit the button.
- 但我不知道他就是Harken  - 开车门吧
See, this is why I need to know what people look like. Man
看吧 这就是为什么我需要知道我们要杀的人长什么样子
You're mad at me for killing him....
你刚刚还生我的气 以为我杀了他...
Can we give him a time-out? For one second.
你能把他锁外面吗? 就一会儿
Make up your fucking mind. It's like...
还用你他妈的脑子瞎编 就好像...
What is this?
这算是什么?
You gotta admit we got some good intel tonight.
你必须要承认 今天我们有搜集到很好的情报
Harken is allergic to peanuts and Pellit's got a huge stash of cocaine.
Harken对花生过敏 而Pellit有一大批可卡因
Are you playing this game? Really?
你们要玩这种游戏吗? 真的要玩?
So all we gotta do is to figure a way to get peanuts somewhere into Harken's house...
那我们要做的 就是想个办法把花生弄进Harken的房间
and put some poison in Pellit's coke.
然后在Pellit的毒品里面下点毒
It's easy for someone to think Pellit got a bad batch of cocaine.
别人很容易就会觉得 Pellit是死于劣质的可卡因
You seriously locking me out of the car like we're in 8th grade?
你们真的把我锁在车外面 好像我们才初中一样?
What about Harken? Probably always got that injector thing.
那Harken怎么办? 他可能随身携带注射器的
Doesn't shower with it.
洗澡总不会带吧
So then we'll put some peanuts, or something, inside his shampoo, I guess.
所以我猜想 我们只要把花生什么的 放进他的沐浴露里面就行
That will be a couple of fatal accidents we're not even there for.
那就是一系列伪造的意外现场 我们甚至都不用现身
- Motherfucker Jones would be so proud.  - Yeah, he would.
- Motherfucker Jones会很骄傲的  - 是啊 他会的
- Getting old.  - What do you do about dummy's boss?
- 岁月不等人啊  - 你准备怎么处理这傻子的老板?
I'll stake her out tomorrow and get to the bottom of it.
我明天会跟踪她 一直跟到晚上
- A man has his limits.  - That left a fucking dent.
- 人的忍耐可是有限度的  - 那一脚他妈可是要留下印子的
Get him fucking home.
他妈的把他送回家吧
Very funny. That was very funny, guys.
好有趣哦 这样真的好有趣哦 伙计们
Dale, we have one thing to figure out, if you can help us out.
Dale 我们还要弄清楚一件事情 如果你能帮我们理清楚的话
If Nick and I were in prison, who do you think would get raped more?
如果Nick和我都去坐牢的话  谁会被强奸的次数会多一点?
Nick.
Nick啊
Really? Why?
真的吗? 为什么啊?
It's about weakness and vulnerability. It's not a looks thing.
这跟怯懦脆弱有关 不是相貌的问题
Good tell, it probably would be Nick.
说得没错 很可能是Nick多吧
Getting locked out of the car is bullshit, man.
被锁出车外面可真扯淡了 伙计们
老鼠药
That's an awesome deal.
这促销太优惠了
Jesus, Dale. It's a murder, not a cocktail party.
天啊 Dale 这是去杀人 不是开鸡尾酒会啊
I know. You don't have to announce that to the world, okay?
我知道 你也用不着说给全世界听吧 行吗?
There was a great deal on nuts. I'm not gonna pass up on savings like that.
花生在搞特卖 我才不会错过这种省钱的机会
Okay, so this is it.
好了 就这么决定了
I'm doing Pellit, you're gonna do Harken,
我搞定Pellit 你搞定Harken
and you'll get some intel from Julia, right?
而你就去Julia那里收集些情报 怎么样?
- Copy that.  - Okay. See you on the other side.
- 了解了  - 好了 牢窗外面见啦
Okay.
好了
- Thank you, Kimmy.  - You're welcome.
- 谢谢啦 Kimmy  - 不用谢
That was great.
太舒服了
- See you next time.  - Yeah.
- 下次再见啦  - 好的
- Thank you, Bill.  - Thank you, Bobby.
- 谢谢啦 Bill  - 要谢你 Bobby
What?
什么?
Whew...
呼...
Oh.
哦
Shit.
见鬼
- Hey.  - How's it going over there?
- 喂  - 你那边怎样了?
- What do you know about Julia?  - I learned I gotta switch dentists...
- 你掌握多少Julia的情报了?  - 我只知道我该换牙医了...
because this woman is unbelievably hot.
因为这个妞正得不敢让人相信啊
- How's it going over there?  - Uh, it's...
- 你那边怎么样?  - 呃 就是...
Just... I'm waiting for, you know, Pellit to sleep or leave or....
我只是... 在等Pellit睡觉啊 出门啊 你懂的...
Just... Just waiting.
就是... 就是在等
Wonder what, uh, Dale's doing with Harken.
呃 不知道Harken那边 Dale做得怎么样了
It's gonna be really hard.
这真的会变的很艰难
And we'll have to work at this every day,
而且我们每天都要为此而努力
but I wanna do that because I want you.
但是我想这么做 因为我想要你
I want all of you forever, you and me, every day...
我想要和你永远在一起 就你和我 每天...
# Everybody was kung-fu fighting #
# 每个人都是功夫高手 #
Give me that.
给我
Give it to me.
把他给我
Jesus. Where does this guy get the energy?
天啊 这个人哪儿这么多精神?
Oh, yeah.
哦 对哦
What the fuck was that?
那个他妈的是什么东西?
Okay. Okay.
好了 好了
- Yeah, Dale?  - I don't think I can do this.
- 喂 Dale?  - 我觉得我下不了手
Look, I know you really hate Harken but...
你瞧 我知道你真的很恨Harken 但是...
I don't think I can go through with it.
我觉得我下不了手
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊 是啊
I know. I've been thinking the same thing.
我知道 我也在考虑同样的事情
- Yeah, let's just call it off.  - What the fuck?
- 对啊 我们就此收手吧  - 他妈的什么情况?
- What?  - It's Harken. He's here.
- 怎么了?  - 是Harken 他在这里
He's at Pellit's? Why?
他在Pellit家? 为什么啊?
I don't know. He's walking right up to the front door.
我不知道 他正站在门口
- You think he's onto us?  - How the fuck do I know?
- 你觉得他在监视我们吗?  - 我他妈怎么会知道?
Knock a little louder?
要再敲得响一点吗?
What? What?
怎么了? 什么事?
Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ, Harken just shot Pellit.
老天爷啊 老天爷啊 Harken刚刚开枪杀了Pellit
Are you sure?
你确定?
Holy shit. Pellit opened up the door, Harken shot him in the chest...
我操 Pellit打开了门 Harken朝他胸口开了一枪...
he fell down, he shot him again in the head.
他倒在地上 他又朝他头开了一枪
He shot him? Wait, what's going on?
他开枪杀了他? 等一下 发生了什么?
I don't understand. What's going on? He shot him?
我没懂 到底发生了什么? 他开枪杀了他?
Nick? Say something. Nick, Nick.
Nick? 说句话啊 Nick Nick
Nick! Nick, Nick, talk to me. Nick, what's happening?
Nick! Nick Nick 和我说句话啊 Nick 发生什么了?
What's going on?
怎么回事情?
- How's Pellit doing?  - Still pretty fucking dead, Dale.
- Pellit怎么样了?  - 他妈死得不能再死了 Dale
I gotta get out of here before somebody sees me.
我要乘没人看到我之前赶快离开这里
Meet me at the bar. I'll call Kurt.
等会儿酒吧见 我打给Kurt
Yeah. I'll meet you there.
好吧 我们到时候见面
I might throw up a couple times in the toilet here,
我可能要在这厕所里吐一会儿
but then I'll meet... I'll meet you there.
但是我会... 我会去那里碰头的
Oh.
哦
Oh, Toyota.
哦 丰田啊
All right, all stay calm. We'll figure this out.
好了 大家冷静 我们会想到办法的
"Calm"? Give my a break. I saw a guy get shot an hour ago.
"冷静"? 省省吧 我一小时前刚刚看到一个人被枪杀
- I know. A guy you were gonna kill anyway.  - Listen, I don't know about that.
- 我知道 这个人反正要被杀掉的  - 听着 我什么都不知道
- What?  - Don't know if I had it in me.
- 什么?  - 我不知道这件事和我有没有关系
I freaked out and panicked, got out of there.
我被吓到恐慌了 快点离开这里
What! Are you fucking kidding? You can't change a plan like this...
什么! 你们他妈耍我吧? 你们不能这样就改变计划...
I'm not a murderer.
我不是个杀人犯
You think when it came down to it, you'd be able to kill Julia?
你觉得等事情平息了 你就能杀掉Julia吗?
I don't know. Maybe you're right. It is a little hard to imagine killing her now.
我不知道 也许你是对的 现在想杀掉她是有点困难
- "Now"?  - Wait, what does that mean?
- "现在"?  - 等一下 这句话什么意思?
- Did you sleep with her?  - No, no.
- 你和她睡过了吗?  - 没有 才没有
- Tell me you didn't sleep with her, dude.  - You're a mess.
- 告诉我 你没有和她睡过 伙计  - 你个掉链子的
But this time it wasn't my fault, I swear to God.
但这次不是我的问题 我对天发誓
You will absolutely be a suspect if you try to kill her now.
如果你现在试着去杀掉她 你明显就是个嫌疑犯
Okay. At first, I was surveilling her, like I was asked to do.
好了 起先 我是在监视她 就像被要求的一样
That is all you ask to do.
你要做的也就只有这些
She's incredibly hot, by the way. So hot.
她正点得太离谱了 顺带提一下 太正点了
Don't talk about how hot she is, bastard.
别这么形容她 你个禽兽
Next thing you know, she starts deliberately undressing.
你要知道接下去 她开始卖弄地脱掉了衣服
Come on.
拜托
In front of her window with the lights on.
站在她窗前 还开着灯
- Like she knew I was watching.  - What is "deliberately undressed"?
- 就好像她知道我在看一样  - 什么叫做"卖弄地脱掉衣服"
Slowly, seductively, lot of shoulder moves...
缓慢的 诱人的 加上很多肩膀的挪动
is clearly putting on a show.
明显就是视觉享受啊
Next thing you know, she makes herself a little snack.
要知道接下去 她给自己做了份小点心
She has a nice chest?
她胸型迷人吗?
A Popsicle.
一根冰棍
- Then a banana.  - Come on.
- 接着是根香蕉  - 拜托
- And finally, a hot dog. I mean, come on.  - God, I don't believe your story.
- 最后 香肠 拜托啊  - 天啊 我不相信你说的了
Three penis-shaped foods, that can't be a coincidence, right?
三个长条状的点心 这不可能是巧合 对吧?
Eating them in that weird order? It's not a proper meal.
还按那种奇怪的顺序吃掉他们? 这些做点心可不合适
It's cold to hot.
这是冰火两重天
Okay, fine. So you took the penis foods as an invitation to fuck her.
好吧 也行 所以你就把长条形的食物当做了干她的提示啦
No, no. God, no. I took her invitation to fuck her as an invitation to fuck her.
没有 才没有 天啊 无所谓提示 她赤裸裸地邀请我干她
She lured me in. It was like one of these things.
她勾引我进去的 就像那种事情一样
There is definitely something clinically wrong with you.
你生理上肯定有问题了
You're a fucking whore.
你他妈就是只鸭
Come on. That's not nice, okay? Look, your problem's solved.
拜托 这难道不好吗 对吧? 你瞧 你的问题解决了
She won't mess with you anymore again to you.
她不会对你死缠烂打了
Can we move on to the business? Let's talk about what happened to Pellit tonight.
我们能谈些正经事吗? 我们谈论一下今晚Pellit的事情
All right, okay. Let me think. Okay, here's what I'm thinking. Here's my idea.
好的 让我想想 对了 我有个主意 是这样的
- We call the cops with an anonymous tip. All right?  - All right.
- 我们用匿名给警察打电话 怎么样?  - 可以
We tell them Harken killed Pellit. Boom!
我们告诉他们 Harken杀了Pellit 嘣!
Harken's in jail, Pellit's in hell, Julia's had the crazy fucked out of her...
Harken进牢房 Pellit进地狱 Julia也有人能够满足她疯狂的欲望了...
and all three of us have our problems solved.
我们三个的问题就这样解决了
It could work. An anonymous tip, that's not bad.
这能行 匿名电话 不错啊
Mm-hm.
嗯哼
Gotta be from a pay phone, though, so it's not traced back to us.
那得有台付费电话 这样就不会查到我们身上
- Exactly.  - Good. Let's take my car. Let's do it.
- 就是这样  - 很好 上车 我们就这么做
All right. Where do you even find a pay phone these days?
好了 现在到哪里能找到付费电话啊?
There's a ton at the bus station for sure.
在汽车站肯定有一堆电话在那里
Oh, yeah, I guess that's a good point. Maybe the mall, probably.
哦 是哦 我猜那里是个好地方 或许商店里也有
What is this?
怎么回事?
- What is this? - Is that for us?
- 这算什么?  - 这是找我们的吗?
- What?  - Oh, shit.
- 什么?  - 哦 见了个鬼
All the way down.
窗户拉到最底下
Right there.
就这样了
- Are you the owner of this vehicle?  - I own it. Yup.
- 你是这辆车的主人吗?  - 这车是我的 是的
We got an APB on a gray Toyota Prius, license 2-Whiskey-Alpha-Quincy-2-3-3.
我们在全境内搜查灰色的丰田普锐斯 车牌2-W-A-Q-2-3-3
- How come?  - Hang on, man.
- 怎么回事?  - 等一下 伙计
- Did I talk to you?  - No.
- 我有在和你说话吗?  - 没有
That's this car. Tell me... tell me how I can help.
就是这辆车 告诉我... 我应该怎么做
A traffic cam caught this car fleeing the scene of a crime tonight.
交通探头拍下这辆车 它逃离了今晚的犯罪现场
- Would you know anything about that?  - I don't know why it would do that.
- 你知道任何相关的事情吗?  - 我不知道为什么会这样
I mean, I don't know. What happened?
我的意思是 我不知道 发生了什么事吗?
- Have you been drinking?  - No.
- 你有喝酒吗?  - 没有
I smell alcohol.
我闻到酒精的味道
- This guy and the mouth in the back. - That's me. My bad.
- 是这个人还有后面那张嘴巴  - 是我 我的错
I'm gonna need you to follow us to the station.
我需要你跟我们去趟局里
Officer.
警官
My man.
小弟
I cannot believe I let you talk me into this whole thing. I cannot believe it.
真不敢相信 我竟答应你们参与整件事情 真不敢相信
Are you kidding me? We were being hypothetical.
你和我开玩笑吧? 我们当时是说说而已
- Being hypothetical?  - You're the one that pushed us into it.
- 说说而已?  - 你才是那个怂恿我们去做的人
Do you wanna explain why you were doing 61 in a 25 zone...
你能解释一下为什么你要在25区闯红灯...
one block from the victim's house...
还离受害者房屋只有一条街区...
just moments after he got shot dead?
而且在他被枪杀之几分钟后?
I was drag racing.
我在飙车
- I'm a drag racer.  - You were drag racing?
- 我是个飙车族  - 你是个飙车族?
Mm.
嗯
In a Prius?
用普锐斯
I don't win a lot.
所以我总是输啊
Here's what I don't understand.
我有点不是很明白
You were at the crime scene.
你当时在犯罪现场
An hour later we find the car. You happened to be hanging with this freaky motherfucker.
一个小时之后 我发现那辆车 你就和这
- A registered sex offender.  - It was an empty playground.
- 一个有记录的性侵者  - 那是个没人的操场
And this guy. Who happens to be working for Pellit Chemicals, the victim's company.
还有这个人 Pellit化工厂的雇员 受害者的雇员
What?
什么
My boss was murdered?
我老板被谋杀了?
Oh, wow. What were you doing at his house, Nick? Why were you there?
哦 哇哦 你在他房前做什么 Nick? 你为什么在那里?
Where were you during the murder?
谋杀发生的时候 你在哪里啊?
I was making love. I was making love to a woman.
我在做爱 我在和一个女人做爱
Yeah. Murdering some ass.
是啊 残害些菊花
- Detectives....  - No, uh, I have a question.
- 警探们...  - 等一下 呃 我有个问题
If one of us knew, you know, who the shooter was...
如果我们中有个人知道谁是枪手的话...
and he was willing to serve you that perp on a platter...
而且愿意为奉上宝贵线索...
he would be entitled to some sort of immunity, right?
他会被给予些赦免权的 对吧?
No. He would be entitled to some jail time.
不会 他只会被判处监禁
If he knew who the shooter was and didn't tell us...
如果他知道谁是枪手 但是不告诉我们的话...
that would be obstruction of justice.
就构成了妨碍司法公正罪
Well, I am glad none of us know who the shooter is.
这样的话 我很庆幸我们中没有人知道谁是枪手
Listen, if you think we're gonna believe that this is all just a big coincidence...
听着 如果你觉得我们会相信 这只是场巨大的巧合的话...
we're gonna be here for a long time.
我们会在这里耗上很长时间
Okay, wait. By saying "we're gonna be here for a long time"...
好的 等一下 说到"我们会在这里耗上很长时间"...
you're implying that we're not allowed to leave...
你是暗指 我们不允许离开...
which would only be the case if we were under arrest. Are we under arrest?
但这只在我们被逮捕的情况下才成立 我们被逮捕了吗?
No. We just brought you in for questioning.
没有 只是带你们回来问话
Well, then, ipso facto...
那这样的话 就此可证...
you don't have sufficient evidence...
你们手头证据不足...
constituting probable cause for an arrest warrant.
无法申请逮捕令
Not yet.
暂时还不够
Well, uh, then, pursuant to the "Fourth Amendment"...
嗯 这样的话 根据"第四修正法案"...
I believe we are free to go. Are we not?
我相信 我们想走就能走 难道不是吗?
Yeah, technically. Yeah.
是的 严格地讲 是的
Technically is good enough for me.
那我们就严格执吧  走人
Gentlemen, ahem, we are free men.
先生们 啊哼 我们都是自由人
Let's go.
我们走吧
- We gotta get back to your car.  - Just keep moving.
- 我们坐你的车回去  - 快走就行了
We get a cab? Take the train? What do you wanna do?
我们打车? 坐火车? 你想要怎么做?
You ever been on a subway in this town?
你坐过城里的地铁没有?
It's pretty great. Where'd that come from?
你刚刚表现不错 那些话从哪儿学来的?
Law & Order, okay? You can learn stuff watching Law & Order.
"法律与秩序" 懂吗? 看它 你能学到几手
- We showed them, huh?  - We did show them.
- 我们让他们见识到了 对吗?  - 我们让他们见识到了
You were about to turn us in.
你刚刚想出卖我们
There was a few conversations about ratting each other out, but it was gonna be fine.
或许有一两句话对我们不利 不过我们会没事的
Hold on.
等等
That's for you, hotshot. Speeding and running a red light.
这是给你的 高手 超速和闯红灯
You boys don't get too comfortable out there.
伙计们 你们出去了也不能逍遥太久
Our forensics team is sweeping the Pellit house right now for DNA and fingerprints.
我们的鉴定科正在Pellit家排查 包括DNA和指纹
And I'll tell you something. They don't miss shit.
我得提醒你们一句 他们不会放过任何蛛丝马迹
In the butt you go, go, go.
搓屁屁呀 搓搓搓
Why would you put his whole bathroom in your ass?!
你把他整个厕所的洗具 都放进了你屁眼?!
- I didn't I know I had DNA in my butt.  - Lying! You know there's DNA in your butt.
- 我不知道屁眼里会有DNA  - 撒谎! 你知道屁眼里会有DNA的
You just like shoving shit in your ass, you fucking pervert!
你只是喜欢捅你的屁眼 你他妈的变态色情狂!
We are lawyering up, man. That's it.
我们去找律师吧 就这么定了
I don't have money for a lawyer. I bought a very expensive ring I can't afford...
我没钱请律师 我买了个昂贵的戒指 我付不起...
then I gave the rest of my motherfucking money to Motherfucker Jones.
然后我把剩下的钱都给了操他妈的Jones
That's who we should talk to.
我们得找他谈谈
- Sure, why not? He's covered us this far, right? Five grand?  - Five thousand. Forty, with the briefcase.
- 好主意 为什么不呢? 这不都他教的吗? 对吗? 五千?  - 是五千零四十 算上箱子的钱
- Shut up about that!  - Shut up about the briefcase.
- 别谈这事了!  - 别提箱子的事了
Excuse me. Excuse me. Da-da-da.
借过 借过
- Hello, Motherfucker. - Hey, look who's back. Look who's back.
- 嗨 操他妈的  - 嗨 看看是谁回来了
Whatever happened to that, uh, strangers on a Train shit?
"火车怪客"计划执行得怎么样了?
Didn't work out. We need your help.
你说的没用 我们需要你的帮助
One of our intended victims killed the other intended victim.
我们某一个目标杀死了另一个目标
- Shut the fuck up.  - It's gone bad.
- 不会吧  - 事情变遭了
You guys are some fucking evil geniuses.
你们真他妈是天才
Thank you, but we had nothing to do with it. We don't know why it happened.
谢谢 不过跟我们无关 我们不知道事情是怎么发生的
Then the cops bring us in as suspects.
而警察们又把我们当成嫌疑犯
Kurt's DNA's all over the apartment because he shoved a toothbrush up his ass.
公寓里到处都有Kurt的DNA 因为他把牙刷捅进了屁眼
- That's not the point.  - I'm giving him the whole story.
- 这不是重点  - 我想让他了解整个故事的经过
I got you. First thing first, we gotta handle business.
我明白 要事先办 我们得解决问题
Mm-hm.
嗯
- I need $5000.  - There's gonna be no more money.
- 我需要五千美金  - 没有钱了
- Two thousand?  - Absolutely not.
- 2000呢?  - 当然没有
No way, Motherfucker. No.
没门儿 操他妈的 没有
All right, look, pay for my drinks.
好吧 听着 帮我买单
- Pay for his drink.  - I'll do that.
- 帮他买单  - 我来吧
Not a very good negotiator.
不是个谈判高手
The guy that killed the other guy, are the cops after him?
警察有没有怀疑 真正的凶手?
No, no, they don't suspect him.
不 不他们没有怀疑他
Then this is what you need to
那么你们就需要这么做
get him to confess to the murder while you're wearing a wire.
带上窃听器 引诱他坦白自己罪行
A wire? We can do that. That's easy.
窃听器? 这我们做得到 这很容易
That how they got you when you murdered somebody?
你当年杀人 就是因此而落网的吗?
- I ain't never murder nobody.  - I'm sorry?
- 我从来没有杀过人  - 什么?
I never murdered anybody.
我从来没有杀过人
Wait, no. You said you did a dime for some pretty nasty shit.
等等 不是吧 你说过你因为违法做了十年的牢
It was some nasty shit, but does that mean I murdered somebody?
的确是违法 不过难道这就意味着我杀了人?
- You implied it.  - You didn't murder someone, what'd you do?
- 你暗示了  - 你没有杀人 那你做了什么?
All right, listen, get in here.
好吧 听着 靠近一点
You guys ever see the movie Snow Falling on Cedars?
你们有没有看过"落在香杉树的雪花"这部电影?
No.
没有
- Never seen that.  - I love that movie.
- 没看过  - 我喜欢那部电影
What happened was is that I took a video camera into the movie and I bootleg it.
事情是这样的 我带着摄影机进影院偷拍
They was waiting right outside the exit. They got me.
他们就等在出口处 抓住了我
- You did 10 years for video piracy?  - Yeah.
- 你因为视频盗版被判了10年?  - 是的
- They take that shit so serious, man.  - Not that seriously.
- 他们真他妈的抓得紧 伙计  - 没有那么严重
We've been taking murder advice...
我们竟向一个外行咨询杀人技巧...
from some guy whose biggest crime is taping an Ethan Hawke movie.
这个人最大的罪行不过是盗版伊桑・霍克电影
- So you do know the movie.  - I know who's in it.
- 所以你知道这部电影  - 我知道谁拍的
Everyone knows the movie. That's not the point. You tricked us, Motherfuck...
每个人都知道这部电影 这不是重点 你耍了我们 操他妈的...
Hang on a second, something doesn't stack up quite right with this, all right?
等等 有个地方对不上 有木有?
So you just call yourself a video pirate, right? Pirating the high seas of videocy?
所以你只是个盗版商 对吗? 在版权的无垠公海中肆意掠夺?
Why do you carry a gun on you, Mr. Video Pirate?
那你为什么要带着枪呢 盗版商先生
- A gun?  - Yeah.
- 一把枪?  - 是的
- I don't wanna see it.  - It's my cell phone.
- 我可不想看见它  - 这是我的手机
- It's a Sidekick. I'm gonna be in the car.  - Oh, shit.
- 这是个插袋 我要回车上了  - 哦 该死的
You grab at it like a gun and you confuse people. Goddamn it, I feel like a moron.
你的动作像是要拿枪 太糊弄人了 该死 我觉得自己像个白痴
- Let's go.  - You are a moron.
- 我们走吧  - 你就是个白痴
Look, you don't go into a bar and hand a guy $5000 just because he's black.
听着 你不该进了酒吧 随随便便给人5000美金 就因为他是黑人
- It was never a black-white thing. - No, come on.
- 这和肤色种族无关  - 算了 快点
Let's go. Come on. Dale.
我们走 快点 Dale
You're all motherfuckers crazy.
一群操他妈的疯子
Okay.
好的
Looks pretty quiet, yeah?
看上去很安静啊?
Yeah, it does. Okay, tape recorder's ready to roll, I got some fresh batteries in here.
是啊 好的 录音机准备好了 我换了新的电池
It was a pretty big investment in my part so I should be the one who does the tape-recording.
这对我来说是笔很大的投资 应该由我来负责录音
- No way. No, I'll do it.  - You're gonna do it?
- 不可能 我来  - 你要录音?
You'll have to duct-tape that to your chest.
你得用胶带把它粘在胸口
I can't tape this to my chest. I have hair on chest.
我不能把这个粘在胸口 我有胸毛
Just put it in your pocket. Not gonna tape it to his chest.
就放在口袋里好了 不用粘在胸口
So, what do we do? Wait for him to come home, we grab a office chair or something?
那么 我们该做什么? 等他回家 我们抓把椅子什么的?
One of us gets in the chair, spins around and dramatically confronts him.
我们当中一个人坐在凳子上转圈 就像电影里那种对质场面
- Great, I'm in the chair.  - Nick's in the chair.
- 那我来负责椅子吧  - Nick负责椅子
- Why are you in the chair?  - He's my boss.
- 为什么你来负责椅子?  - 他是我的恶老板
Maybe we should get three chairs and all spin around at the same time.
或许我们可以准备三把椅子 一起转
Confront him like that.
这样效果比较强
That's not intimidating, that's like a musical number.
这一点也没气势 像是在演音乐剧
Watch out for the cat.
小心猫
Surprise!
惊喜!
Okay. It's a false alarm. Just mingle, mingle, mingle.
这是个假警报  保持原样 保持原样
Hi. Who are you?
嗨 你们是谁?
Come inside. Close that door. Hurry.
进来吧 关上门 快点
Um, okay. Now, wait a minute.
呃 好的 等等
You're the young man who helped Dave out on the street the other night.
你就是那天晚上在街上救了Dave的年轻人
- That's him.  - Yeah, that's who I am.
- 就是他  - 啊 是我
- How is he?  - He is great, thanks to you. Thank you.
- 他怎么样?  - 他很好 谢谢你
- Did I invite you?  - You did and you didn't.
- 我邀请你了吗?  - 你有 你没有
I work with your husband. We're late.
我是你丈夫的同事 我们迟到了
- I'm Nick. These are my plus-twos.  - He's in the garage.
- 我叫Nick 他们是和我一起来的  - 他在车库里
Oh, we should hide. Everybody, come on in.
哦 我们得躲起来 大家 快过来
- Someone get the lights.  - Get down, get down, get down.
- 谁关下灯  - 蹲下 蹲下
I'm Kurt, by the way. I didn't get a chance to introduce myself at the door.
顺便提一下 我叫Kurt 刚刚在门口没机会介绍我自己
- Oh, hey, Rhonda. Hi.  - Hi, Rhonda. Very nice to meet you.
- 哦 嗨 我叫Rhonda  - 嗨 Rhonda 很高兴认识你
Nick didn't tell me his boss was married to a model.
Nick没对我说过他的老板娶了个模特
Ha, ha. Yeah, not a model.
呵呵 不是模特
When did you quit?
你什么时候退出的?
Surprise!
惊喜!
Goddamn it! God, I hate that!
该死的! 天呐 我讨厌这玩意儿!
We got you, huh, honey?
我们吓到你了吗 亲爱的?
- So you were surprised?  - Yeah.
- 你被吓到了?  - 是的
Look, sweetie, everybody's here.
听着 亲爱的 大家都在这儿
I'm gonna put my stuff down.
我得把东西放下
She knows I hate surprises.
她知道我讨厌惊喜
I think we got him. Ha, ha. We got him good.
我想我们吓到他了 呵呵 我们做得不错
Okay.
好吧
He's gone off on his own. This is our chance.
他一个人进去了 这是我们的机会
- You guys ready?  - Yeah, very ready.
- 你们准备好了吗?  - 是的 准备好了
Stay close, okay?  Mm-hm.
机灵点 好吗? 嗯
Let's do it. Let's do it.
开始吧 开始
Harken.
Harken啊
I cannot believe my wife invited you.
真不敢相信我老婆居然邀请你来
What are you doing here? Come to stab me a few more times?
你来这儿做什么? 多刺我几下?
- We know what you did.  - Well, what does that mean?
- 我们知道你的所作所为了  - 哦 这话是什么意思?
We were there. We saw you kill him.
我们当时在场 我们看到你杀了他
Really?
真的吗?
So, what is this, then? Your little shakedown?
那 这算什么? 来敲诈的?
You think that you can blackmail me...
你们觉得自己有种敲到我头上来...
because you saw me kill my wife's lover?
就因为看到我杀了我妻子的情人?
Say his name!
把名字说出来!
What?
什么?
The man you killed, you say his name.
你杀的人 把名字说出来
Pellit? Trust me, Pellit's name means nothing anymore.
Pellit吗? 相信我 Pellit这个名字已经不再有任何意义了
There it is. Thank you. Let's do it, guys.
到点子上了 谢谢你 我们走 兄弟们
- Yeah, that's right.  - Hang on. Where the fuck is Kurt?
- 是啊 没错  - 等等 他妈的Kurt到哪儿去了?
I killed Pellit.
是我杀了Pellit
Hold that thought, I'm missing my friend Kurt.
过会儿再说 我找不到我的朋友Kurt了
I walked right up to his door, I put a gun in his chest and I shot him.
我径直走到他门前 用枪抵住他的胸口 枪杀了他
Then you know what? You know what I did after that? I shot him again.
然后 你知道怎么样了吗? 你知道之后我干了什么吗? 我又开了一枪
And let me tell you something.
让我告诉你件事
I liked it.
我很喜欢这种感觉
So if you think that I'm some sort of pussy...
如果你们以为我是个软蛋...
who won't do exactly the same thing to a couple of lame-assed blackmailers...
没胆对一群狗娘养的勒索者作出同样的事情的话...
think again.
好好想想
Know who thinks you're a pussy? My friend Kurt. Let me grab him.
知道是谁觉得你是软蛋吗? 我朋友kurt 让我去找到他
You are pathetic, Hendricks.
你们真可悲 Hendricks
You walk into my house on my goddamn birthday and pull this shit.
你们走进我的家 在我该死的生日会上挑明这件事
Well, let me tell you something.
哦 让我告诉你些事
You're dead.
你们死定了
You and you.
你 还有你
- And...?  - Kurt.
- 还有...?  - Kurt
Kurt. Dead men.
Kurt 死定了
I didn't know it was your birthday. What's he doing?
我不知道今天是你的生日 他在做什么?
- What do you got?  - Getting my gun. Only take a second.
- 你在找什么?  - 找我的枪 一会儿就好
- I'll get the car.  - I'll go.
- 我要回车上去  - 我也去
We had him, we had the whole goddamn thing. What the fuck happened to Kurt?
我们拿到了 都拿到了 该死的Kurt去哪儿了?
- Hey!  - There you are.
- 嗨!  - 是你们啊
Where were you?
你到哪儿去了?
My, uh, stomach was bothering me. Had to use the bathroom.
我 呃 胃不太舒服 刚上了厕所
He confessed everything, now he's getting his gun.
他都招了 现在在找他的枪
- Kurt, what happened there?  - Oh, uh...
- Kurt 发生了什么?  - 哦 呃...
she was giving me a tour of the mouth... House.
她带我参观一下嘴... 是房子
- Ow! What are you...?  - Get in the car. Right now.
- 哦! 你怎么能...?  - 上车 马上
Knock it off.  Come on.
别吵了 快点
Look, I wasn't thinking, okay? I'm sorry.
听着 我不想的 好吗? 我错了
She's just very hot. And I'm weak. I'm a weak, weak man, okay?
她太辣了  我很弱 我经受不了诱惑 行了吧?
I admit it.
我承认
- Back it up, back it up.  Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- 倒车 倒车   - 哦 该死的
- They found my DNA.  - Back it up.
- 他们发现我的DNA了  - 后退
Go backwards. Go backwards. See? They found your poop brush.
后退 快后退 看见没? 他们发现了你沾了大便的牙刷
- You are obsessed with your asshole!  - No, I'm not. It was a prank, Dale.
- 你痴迷于自己的屁眼!  - 不 我没有 那只是个恶作剧 Dale
Shut it down. Let's start talking about where we're gonna live.
闭嘴 我们该讨论一下我们该住哪儿
- The current situation won't work.  - Yeah, exactly. There'll be cops everywhere.
- 我们不能住在家里了  - 完全正确 到处都是条子
You talking about fleeing the country?
你们是在谈论外逃吗?
Damn right. I'm talking about Canada or Mexico.
该死的 是的 我在考虑加拿大或者是墨西哥
I can't live in Mexico. I mean, I can't handle the food.
我不能住在墨西哥 我是说 我不能习惯那里的食物
My digestion alone... I'll probably die.
单从我的消化系统来说... 我可能会死
- You'd rather be in jail the rest of your life?  - Shut the fuck up.
- 难道你想在监狱中渡过余生吗?  - 给我闭嘴
I'm getting a call. I gotta get this. Hello?
电话响了 我得接 嗨?
Hello, lover.
嗨 小情人
Uh, look, Julia, now's not a good time to talk.
呃 听着 Julia 现在可不是谈话的好时机
- Hey, I'm not here.  - That's okay.
- 嗨 当我不在  - 没关系
I actually meant to call your home phone.
事实上我想打你家里的电话
You know, tell Stacy about us.
告诉Stacy我们之间的事
- No, don't do that. Wait. Wait.   - We'll learn the metric system.
- 哦 别这么做 等等  - 我们得学会用公制单位
We gotta buy coats and sweaters and learn hockey and all that shit.
我们得买大衣和毛衣 学会打曲棍球和其他莫名其妙的东西
No, I think I've waited long enough, Dale.
不 Dale 我想我已经等得不耐烦了
I'm sort of tired of you toying with my emotions.
我有点厌倦你玩弄我的感情
I'm not playing with you.
我没有玩弄你的感情
I'm not toying with you. I'm gonna take care of it. I'm gonna take care of it.
我没有玩弄你 我会处理的 我会处理的
Wait, wait, wait. What are you gonna do to me?
等等 你想对我怎么样?
- I'm gonna have sex with you.  - What?
- 我要和你做爱  - 什么?
I want you to give me details, you little pussy.
我想听具体点的 小猫咪
And please be explicit.
讲清楚点
Details? I'm in a car with people. Now is not a good time for details.
细节? 我现在在车里 车上还有其他人 现在不是说细节不太合适
- I don't care if it's not a great time.  - Okay, fine.
- 我不在乎现在是不是适合  - 好的 行
I'm gonna make you feel good. You know?
我会让你很舒服 你知道吗?
With my fingers and my tongue and whatnot.
用我的手指和舌头(TBD)
I know you can do better than that.
我知道你远不止这两下子
All right, I'm gonna put my penis in your pussy, Julia.
好吧 我会把我的鸡鸡填满你的阴门 Julia
Oh, boy, that's gonna get me done.
哦 伙计 说得我受不了了
What the fuck was that?
操 那是什么玩意儿?
- What the fuck?  - That's Harken. Lose him.
- 什么东西?  - 是Harken 甩掉他
- Oh, my God!  - Get out of here.
- 哦 天呐!  - 快离开这儿
Look, careful.
看 小心
Hey, are you gonna slap me in the face with your cock, Dale?
嗨 你会用你的鸡鸡抽打我的脸吗 Dale?
Yes, I'll slap you in the face with my cock!
是的 我会用鸡鸡打你的脸!
- This guy's fucking crazy.  - Slap you all over your face with my cock!
- 操这男人疯了  - 用我的鸡鸡抽打你的脸!
- Don't get in a wreck.  - It's go time.
- 不要被撞扁了  - 全速前进
Okay. More, Dale.
可以 更多 Dale
I will go up and down on you...
我会在你身上上下翻滚
and I'll rub my naked butt against your naked butt...
用我赤裸的屁股顶撞你赤裸的娇臀...
until it's raw and red...
直到撞得生疼发红...
and we're both really chafed up real bad.
我们身体都变得火热
Not good. Get us out of here! Get us out of here!
不太好 快让我们出来! 快让我们出来!
I got it, I got it.
我明白了 我明白了
- Come on. - I'll spit on your arms and stuff.
- 快点  - 我会射在你的胳膊和其它部位上
- What else?  - And then I'm gonna...
- 还有呢?  - 然后我要...
jam my skull into the crack of your ass!
把头塞进你屁股缝里!
Yeah, baby. In the crack of your ass.
是的 宝贝 你屁股缝里
And I'll dance on your boobies, and I'll jump up and down on your butt.
而且我要在你双峰之上跳舞 给你臀部上上下下的享受
Ah. I'll see you Friday, dirty bird.
呃 我们星期五见 小色狼
Good. Friday. See you Friday.
好吧 星期五 星期五见
Nice job fucking the crazy out of her, Kurt!
都是你惹出来的火 Kurt 叫你干她!
Sorry, maybe I should have been dancing on her boobs, huh?
或许我应该在她双峰之上跳舞的 是吧?
Maybe you should have.
或许你就该这么做
That was very good driving, by the way.
顺便说下 你车开得真不错
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
- Good evening, Mr. Buckman.  - Yeah, hey, Gregory. How are you?
- 晚上好 Buckman先生  - 嘿 Gregory 你好吗?
Our onboard sensors report you've had a collision.
我们的车载传感器感应到车体刚刚发生碰撞
That's because we have a crazy man that hit us.
那是因为有个疯子在撞我们
I will alert the authorities and direct them to your location.
我会通知警局并指引他们来你们这里
Don't call the cops. They're already after us.
别打电话给警察 他们已经在追我们了
No, Gregory, they think we murdered someone, all right?
不要 Gregory 他们认为我们杀了人 知道吗?
Do not call the cops.
不要打电话给警察
What's going on? Why you slowing down, Kurt?
什么情况? 你为什么减速 Kurt?
Whoa. Oh, no, no, no. I didn't do that. No, the engine died.
喔 不 不 不 我没减速 不是我 发动机出问题了
- I have remotely disabled your engine.  - What?
- 是我遥控终止了你的动力系统  - 什么?
It is standard Nav Guide protocol...
这是Nav Guide系统在驾驶员出现违法行为的时候
whenever a driver has committed a crime.
所采取的标准处理办法
I pay 19 bucks a month for this fucking service.
这他妈的导航服务是我每个月交了十九美元的
Remain with your vehicle. The police will be arriving shortly.
不要下车 警察马上就到
Gregory, I thought you were our fucking friend, man!
Gregory 我还以为你他妈的是我们的朋友呢 哥们!
Get out of the car, all of you. Come on. Come on.
你们都下车 快点 赶紧
- Remember I saved your life that one time?  - Shut up.
- 还记得我救过你一命吗?  - 闭嘴
- Just take it easy with that...  - Shut up.
- 你别冲动...  - 闭嘴
I got six bullets in this gun.
我这把枪有六发子弹
Which means I can shoot all of you twice, just like that bastard Pellit...
那就意味着我可以给你们每人两枪 就像我杀Pellit那混蛋时一样...
if I really wanted to,
如果我真想杀你们的话
but I'm not gonna do that.
但我不会这样做
You're not gonna shoot us twice or not gonna shoot us? Be clear.
你是说不给我们每人两枪 还是根本不杀我们? 说清楚点
Shut up.
闭嘴
I got a better idea. I'm gonna tell the cops that you killed Pellit.
我有个更好的主意 我要告诉警察是你们杀了Pellit
And when I found out, you tried to kill me to shut me up.
被我发现以后 你们试图杀我灭口
- That's crazy.  - Is it?
- 这也太疯狂了  - 是吗?
Because I don't see one shred of evidence that proves that I shot Pellit.
因为没有任何证据能证明是我杀了Pellit
And besides, I'm the guy with the bullet in his leg.
而且我腿上还中了一枪
What?
什么?
God, that hurts so much.
天啊 疼死我了
Son of a bitch.
狗娘养的
- Catch!  - No, don't ca...
- 接着!  - 别 别接...
- God damn it, Dale.  - You see?
- 该死 Dale  - 你看见没有?
You can't win a marathon without putting some Band-Aids on your nipples.
不经历风雨 怎么见彩虹
- What does that mean?  - Watch this.
- 你这话是什么意思?  - 看着
- Everybody freeze!  - Police!
- 所有人都不许动!  - 警察!
Drop the gun! On your knees!
放下枪! 跪在地上!
Thank God. Officers, thank God you're here.
谢天谢地 警官先生你们终于来了
These guys, they shot me.
这些家伙 他们开枪打伤我
- That's not true!  - That's bullshit!
- 那不是事实!  - 他胡说!
I found out they murdered someone. They tried to shut me up.
我发现他们杀了人 他们就要杀我灭口
Please protect me from them. I have a wife and a cat!
求你们保护我 我家里还有妻子 和一只猫!
All right, take it easy. Call for an ambulance.
好的 别紧张 打电话叫救护车
- Hey, what is this?  - It's nothing. It's just a tape recorder.
- 嘿 这是什么?  - 没什么 只是个录音机
Oh, shit! It's a tape recorder!
噢 天啊! 这是个录音机!
- A tape recorder. Did you turn that off?  - No, it's been recording!
- 是录音机 你关掉了吗?  - 没有 一直在录!
- So listen to us, officer.  - Hands up!
- 听我们说 警官先生  - 举起手来!
Listen to us for one second. He confessed to killing Pellit.
听我们说句话 他亲口承认杀害Pellit
He said he shot him twice...
他说他给了他两枪...
and he was gonna shoot us once or twice. He was unclear about that.
还说要给我们一两枪 他没说清楚到底是一枪还是两枪
- You are insane.  - Just play the tape.
- 你疯了  - 放录音吧
But all those people are just right outside.
可所有人都在外面呢
Your balls are so smooth.
你的蛋蛋好光滑啊
Wait a minute. Is that my wife?
等一下 那是我妻子吗?
No, no. Of course not, no. Let's move past that.
不 不 当然不是 跳过这部分吧
jam my skull into the crack of your ass!
把头塞进你屁股缝里!
I'll dance on your boobies, and jump up and down on your butt.
而且我要在你双峰之上跳舞 给你臀部上上下下的享受
What the fuck is this?
这他妈的是什么?
Don't judge. I have a thing with my boss. It's none of your business.
别指责我 我和我老板之间有点事情 这不关你的事
If you could get to the end...?
如果你跳到最后一部分...?
There's nothing on here.
什么都没有
- Shit!  - What happened?
- 该死!  - 怎么了?
Thing must have stopped when we crashed.
这东西肯定在我们撞车的时候停止录音了
Yeah. Right before this guy supposedly confessed?
正好在这家伙要承认罪行之前停止了?
I told you, these guys are liars. They cannot be trusted.
我告诉过你 这些家伙都是骗子 不能相信他们
They shot me in the leg, killed a guy.
他们朝我腿上开了一枪 还杀了个人
- He shot himself.  - I don't need to hear anything else.
- 他自己朝自己开的枪  - 我不想再听下去了
- Cuff them.  - Oh, my God.
- 把他们铐起来  - 噢 我的天啊
- You don't need to cuff us.  - My God, we're going to jail.
- 你不需要铐我们  - 我的天啊 我们要进监狱了
We're going to jail. Unbelievable.
我们要进监狱了 真不敢相信
It hurts. It hurts so much.
好痛 痛死我了
Excuse me? Officers?
警官先生 能打扰一下吗?
I should mention that it is Nav Guide policy...
我应该提到Nav Guide公司政策规定...
to record all conversations for quality assurance.
为保证服务质量 我们需要记录所有对话
- Who the hell's that? - That's our Nav Guide rep.
- 这他妈的是谁?  - 这是我们Nav Guide导航系统代表
- His name is Almonan.  - Hands up!
- 他叫Almonan  - 举起手来!
- Atmanad.  - Almondmond.
- Atmanad  - 是Almondmond
- Atmanad is what it was!   - Atmanand.
- 他肯定叫Atmanad!  - Atmanand
Atmand... Gregory, uh, play what he said.
Atmand... Gregory 播放他说的话
- Play it just after the crash.  - Very good, sir.
- 只放撞击之后那部分就好  - 好的 先生
You're not gonna listen to this. This isn't evidence.
你不会听这个东西的吧 这能不算是证据
I got six bullets in this gun.
我这把枪有六发子弹
Which means I can shoot all of you twice, just like that bastard Pellit...
那就意味着我可以给你们每人两枪 就像我杀Pellit那混蛋时一样...
if I really wanted to,
如果我真想杀你们的话
but I'm not gonna do that.
但我不会这样做
- That's it.  - So it was you.
- 就是这个  - 这么说真是你
That is not proof. That's just a car. You're not gonna listen to a car.
那不能算证据 那只是辆车而已 你不会相信一辆车说的话吧
Looks like I'm getting that promotion after all. Yeah.
看起来我终究还是要升职了
To answer your question, that was your wife.
回答你刚才的问题 那就是你妻子
- You fucked my wife?  - I fucked your wife.
- 你干了我的妻子?  - 我干了你的妻子
You fucked my wife!
你干了我的妻子!
Ah.
嗷
How you like them nipples?
这一拳你觉得怎么样?
Did you just do the catchphrase?
你刚玩了猜词游戏吗?
- Good Will Hunting.  - Good Will Hunting.
- "心灵捕手"  - "心灵捕手"
- That's so great.  - I caught it, yeah.
- 真不错啊  - 是的 我猜出来了
Good Will Hunting rip. Instead of saying "apples" he said "nipples."
是"心灵捕手"暗语 他没说"苹果"(拳头) 说的"乳头"
- Felt like a moment.  - And happy birthday.
- 感觉是值得纪念的一刻  - 生日快乐
So in the end, we didn't wind up going to jail.
最后 我们没有进监狱
Actually, we did later that night when they booked us.
实际上 我们还是进去备案了
But since we led the cops to Harken...
但因为我们帮警察抓住了Harken...
they ultimately agreed to let our other offenses slide.
他们最后同意撤消对我们其它违法行为的起诉
Strangely enough, lucky for Kurt...
说起来也奇怪 算Kurt走运...
there's no laws on the books against putting people's toiletries up your ass.
没有法律规定不能把别人的洗漱用品在屁股上蹭
Anyway, with Harken in his new position...
总之 因为Harken有了新的职位...
on all fours in prison for 25 to life, Comnidyne made me acting president.
在监狱里蹲二十五年到无期 Comnidyne公司升我做代理总裁
It's a great job, I got a solid raise and I'm actually my own boss.
是份很好的工作 我涨了很多薪水 而且我自己就是老板
Well, except for the CEO.
除了公司的首席执行官
- Morning.  - Oh, morning. You, uh, must be Nick.
- 早上好  - 噢 早上好 你一定就是Nick吧
- I am.  - Well, it's great to finally meet you.
- 我是  - 好的 很高兴终于能见到你
- You too, Mr. Sherman.  - Please. Lou.
- 我也是 Sherman先生  - 叫我Lou吧
Okay. Lou.
好的 Lou
I want you to know that I appreciate the opportunity you've given me.
非常感谢你能给我这次机会
I won't let you down.
我不会让你失望的
Yeah, I'm sure you won't, son.
是啊 我相信你会做得很好 小伙子
From what I hear, people say he's the nicest guy in the world.
我听别人说他是世界上最和善的人
Mr. Sherman, I'm sorry your coffee was cold.
Sherman先生 很抱歉你的咖啡凉了
Uh, Lou?
噢 Lou?
Most people.
大多数人
Mr. Sherman, I'm hungry!
Sherman先生 我饿了!
Can I come out now, please?
求求你 能放我出来吗?
- You hear that?  - No.
- 你听见了吗?  - 没有
Sounds like there's someone in your trunk.
听起来有个人在你后备箱里
Nick, Why don't we let this be, uh, our little secret?
Nick 就当这是我们两个的小秘密 好吧?
I need a shower.
我得洗澡
Yeah. Turns out my new boss...
是的 结果我的新老板...
is a twisted old fuck.
是个老变态
Meanwhile, the Pellit family put the most senior person in charge of the company...
与此同时 Pellit family公司让资历最老的员工暂时管理公司
which wasn't Kurt. But he was okay with that.
这个人不是Kurt 但他可以接受
Because he realized that when you're the boss,
因为他发现当你是老板的时候
sometimes people want you dead.
有时员工希望你去死
- Hey, Kurt. Come in.  - Margie, I wanted to congratulate you.
- 嘿 Kurt 进来吧  - Margie 我想祝贺你
Thank you.
谢谢
If there's anything I can do obviously to help out
在你生小孩以前有什么需要我帮忙的地方
before the baby gets here, just let me know.
你尽管告诉我
- What baby?  - Your baby.
- 什么孩子?  - 你的孩子
- I'm not pregnant.  - So I'm just touching you?
- 我没有怀孕  - 那我摸的就是你?
Ay.
呀
Julia.
Julia啊
I was thinking perhaps we could drill the patient first.
我觉得或许我们可以先拿病人练习一下
And Dale?
至于Dale呢?
Ultimately, he decided his only choice was to screw Julia after all.
最终他发现他唯一的出路就是去陷害Julia
You just continue to surprise me...
你真是让我惊喜不断啊...
you dirty, dirty little man.
你个色色的小可爱
Just you wait.
你就瞧好吧
You like that, Dale?
Dale 你喜欢这样吗?
- You like that, Dale?  - Oh, my God, yeah.
- Dale 你喜欢这样吗?  - 噢 天啊 就是这样
Oh.
噢
Oh, gosh, do I wish I could have sex with Julia.
哦 天啊 我希望我可以和Julia做爱
What?
什么?
I'm so sorry, but I couldn't keep it together! It's amazing!
真对不起 但我实在忍不住了! 这太棒了!
- She was talking to your penis!  - Who are you?
- 她刚对你的小弟弟说话!  - 你是谁?
Julia, this is my good friend, Kenny Sommerfeld.
Julia 这是我的好朋友Kenny Sommerfeld
Most Likely to Succeed.
最有可能成功的方法
- Give me some of that.  - Don't you touch me.
- 来和我亲热下  - 不要碰我
Now, Kenny here, he'll do just about anything for 50 bucks.
这个Kenny 给他五十美元 他就能帮你做任何事
- Yeah, it's true.  - Yeah, and it's not pretty.
- 是 没错  - 是的 而且一点也不光彩
But that's why I asked him to help me frame you.
但正因为这样我才让他帮我陷害你
Really? Is this all you've got? Your word against mine?
真的? 你就这点本事? 别人凭什么相信你?
Don't forget about that guy.
别忘了那边那家伙
Say hi to my cameraman. He's filmed a lot of Hollywood hits.
跟我的摄影师打个招呼吧 他拍了很多好莱坞电影
You are a sick little bastard.
你个无耻的小混蛋
Shut the fuck up for a second.
你他妈的给我安静一下
Julia, shut the fuck up for a second, all right?
Julia 你他妈的给我闭嘴 好吗?
Now, here's what's gonna happen, okay?
现在 按照我说的去做 好吧?
I'm going to take a very nice, very expensive two-week vacation with my fiancee.
我要和我的未婚妻一起去度两个星期的豪华假期
Let's call it a honeymoon, all right? And you are gonna pay for it.
我们叫度蜜月 好吧? 一切费用都由你承担
Then I'm going to return to a rape-free workplace, all right?
我回来以后需要不会遭到性骚扰工作环境 明白吗?
Because if you so much as look at my sexy little ass, Julia...
因为只要你看一眼我性感的小屁股 Julia...
I will have yours locked the fuck up...
你就等着蹲监狱吧...
you crazy bitch whore!
你个疯婊子!
Ah, that felt good.
啊 太痛快啦
How's the hair? Is it good, is it great? It's not as bad as his, is it?
我头发怎么样? 可以吧 非常好吗? 不像他的那么难看吧?
I had no idea that you called your grandmother "Gam Gam."
我不知道你管你奶奶叫"Gam Gam"
Calm down!
冷静下来!
Oh!
噢!
Holy shit. He went out the door.
天啊 他从车门掉出去了
This place is awful. It's like The Sharper Image took a shit in here.
这地方好可怕啊 感觉所有东西都是从"尖端印象"(新品销售商)买的
Five forty, with the briefcase.
连公文包一起四百五十美元
Oh, shut up about the briefcase.
噢 别提那公文包了
Gonna put that "briefcabe" up my ass.
我要把那"公文飚"夹在我屁股里
I'm gonna put that briefcase up my ass!
我要把那公文包夹在我屁股里
A dancin' girl
一个舞女
- You're good? He's good.  - Yeah, I'm okay.
- 你没事了? 他没事了  - 是的 我挺好的
Or else little Stacy here's gonna get a little peek...
否则小Stacy就会瞟到...
at my photo album.
我的像册
One more. Let's fix this.
再来一次 我们把这个修好
Have you ever in your life seen this much co...?
你这辈子有没有见过这么多可卡...?
Let's...
让我们...
Now I'm sneezing dust bunnies. Is that diabetes?
你看我打喷嚏打出这么多灰尘 是糖尿病吗?
I'm a pharmacist, not a doctor.
我只是个药剂师 不是医生
Is that my brain? Take my temperature.
是从我脑袋里出来的吗? 给我量量体温
Have you any, uh, roofies?
你这里有春药吗?
I want a lollipop. Do you like karaoke?
我要棒棒糖 你喜欢卡拉OK吗?
Do you have MDMA? I'll suck your d...
你有摇头丸吗? 我要帮你吹...
Shit happens.
天有不测风云
What is your projected outside date of completion, Motherfucker?
你计划什么时候下手 Motherfucker?
Give me that again.
还是再说一遍吧
- Oh, hi! Hi! Hello.  - Hi.
- 噢 嗨! 嗨! 你好  - 嗨
Come on, what are you...?
拜托 你在干什...?
Wouldn't mind bending her over a barrel and showing her the 50 states, right?
愿意干得她满天星吧?
I don't know what that means.
我不知道你在说什么
- It's a phrase.  - I don't think so.
- 这是个习语  - 我不这么认为
Yeah, it is. It certainly is. Yeah, it definitely is.
是的 就是习语 肯应是 绝对是
- Really?  - Yeah, it's from a movie.
- 真的吗?  - 是电影里的对白
Uh-uh.
呃
It is now.
从现在开始就是了
Beautiful.
说得好
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：嘿疯
翻译：煦煦 D调的张扬 草长莹霏 RK翔 小花~  回声 CHI
校对：柚子茶 月光取暖